What's up?
I'm back.
Did I scare ya?
Huh?
We're drinking a little bit of alcohol today.
Just a tiny bit.
Guys, I've been so busy lately.
That's why I haven't been streaming or putting up videos on YouTube.
But it's over.
I had to...
fix up the old apartment before I handed it off to the next tenant, you know?
And... So I put up the soundproofing, right?
In the old apartment.
The panels.
And I made a huge mistake.
Because on half of them, I used glue.
Because there's concrete.
I couldn't put in nails.
Or screws, right?
Man, that glue is strong.
That is... That's crazy.
It took me multiple days just to scratch that shit off.
It was bad.
I will never do that again.
That is horrible.
My hands are completely fucked at this point.
Like, they are so sore.
It's crazy.
I feel like it wasn't even worth it to do.
You know, I should have just taken a bill and have someone do it or something.
Because this killed me, man.
Yeah.
The funny thing is, when I tried to put it up, the glue wouldn't even hold.
Like, what the... What is this shit glue?
You know?
It's not even gonna fit.
Or it's not... Like, I barely made it stay on.
And now I couldn't get it off.
Crazy.
Adhesive strips?
Dude, these are, like, huge panels that weigh a lot.
I don't think that's gonna be enough.
I learned my lesson, though.
I will never do that again.
Never.
Dude, I didn't see the eclipse.
I didn't.
Because right before it happened, my friend called me and I totally forgot all about it.
And I was on the phone with him.
And then afterwards, they were like, fuck.
But then I heard from other people in my area that there was cloudy weather anyway.
And, you know, the sun was quite low on the horizon.
So I probably wouldn't have been able to see it anyway, Copium.
Yeah, I probably wouldn't have been able to see it anyway, you know?
Oh, man, that sucks.
Dude, I'm the fakest astrophysicist.
It's not very cool unless it's total.
Totally, man.
I agree with you.
Man, I haven't been playing any games at all except one or two deadlock matches in the last, like, four or five days.
Insanity.
We're gonna get back to it, though.
We're gonna play Minecraft.
I'm also gonna start a new stream game soon.
So we're gonna have two concurrently running.
And I may actually just retire, um...
The Binding of Isaac for now.
I don't feel like playing it right now.
You know?
At least for now.
We'll see.
It's too damn hard, man.
And then, of course, we have, um...
The robot game.
Detroit Become Human.
What you see on YouTube is everything I've played.
I haven't even played since.
That's how busy I've been.
And the few times I've had time, I just wasn't in the headspace for that, you know?
Man, oh man.
So.
But now all that is over.
I left them the keys.
The apartment is out of my head.
I don't have to think about it anymore.
It's gone.
Now I can think about...
The games.
Just here to shout out the Andor references in previous streams as no one hyped it.
Wait, did I make Andor references?
What did I say?
Except saying that it was good.
Did I make some kind of really sick reference?
What rank are you on Deadlock?
I'm not even ranked, man.
I just started again since...
Well, since I played it on the channel, like, almost a year ago.
The game is so different.
I've been playing some Infernus.
And some McGuinness.
Those are, like, the two only heroes I remember how to play, sort of.
The whole map is different now.
It's weird.
Jackie is completely settled in.
She is, uh, living her best life right now.
How's the clock tower that was planned to be built?
Uh, you'll see.
It's amazing.
It's one of the best creations I've made, Big Papa.
You're gonna be proud of me.
I will show the clock tower off in exactly 37 minutes.
So get ready for that.
Please collect all the armor trim out there.
I'll try.
Because I haven't actually done that very much in the past.
Mostly because you don't see your character anyway.
So why would you even wanna, you know, customize the character?
Doesn't really, you know, get me going at all.
The idea of that.
Oh, I'm showing my clock on stream.
What's my favorite mob in Minecraft?
That's a good question.
Which mob do I really enjoy seeing?
You know, when I see the mob, I go, oh yeah, that's nice.
That's a good mob.
Hmm.
Which one would that be?
Maybe, I don't know.
Maybe a sheep.
I kinda, I like looking at them.
That's nice.
I like sheep.
The way they go, meh.
Or also the cows.
I love the way they go, moo.
You know?
That's the shit.
Yeah.
ODB!
That's, hold on a minute.
We haven't even found one of those in this world yet.
Armadillo.
Oliver, in all your wisdom, what is your tip for staying fit?
Dude, I cannot give wisdom on that.
Cause I'm not fit right now.
I have a tiny, middle-aged beer belly.
That has developed over the last couple months.
I'm gonna work it off, though.
That shall come off.
I'm not the guy to ask, okay?
I'm not very active.
At least not right now.
I have a dad bod without being a dad.
I even do the dad sneeze, I noticed the other day, you know?
I don't sneeze normally anymore.
I scream when I sneeze.
I feel like something's happening at 34 years old, you know?
You become different.
34 is not yet middle-aged.
Is it not?
It's like...
Okay, maybe not.
It feels like it is, though.
Sneeze at Mach 10.
Yeah, the transition has begun.
Remember the days when the guy went jogging at 1am?
Dude, I...
Yeah, man.
It'll happen again.
New apartment, new life.
Fresh cut.
So hot, you know?
Except I don't have a fresh cut.
I just made that up.
I lied.
I don't know why, but I expected you to be older.
Wait, more old than 34?
I feel like 34 is quite old for a gamer nowadays.
Most of these Twitch streamers are, like, in their 20s.
Early 20s.
And they have, like, Lamborghinis.
Mansions.
You know?
34 is decrepit.
Yeah, I mean...
Sure feels like it sometimes.
You seem like a 25-year-old to me.
I guess it's the voice.
I have quite a light voice.
Right?
It's not very deep.
I wish I had a deep voice.
I would love to be able to do some kind of...
I don't know.
Voice over for a nature documentary or something.
You sound like 20, 30?
Okay.
Well, that's good.
I'm glad.
If I recall correctly, there are some OG Minecraft streamers that are closer to or at 40 now.
I mean...
If they've been playing it since Minecraft came out...
I get it, you know?
If they were in their 20s while doing it.
Or 25 or so.
The game is like 10 years old now, right?
Maybe even more.
I know three languages, Joxy.
Dude, it's so weird streaming again.
Even though it's just been five days.
I feel like I haven't even been in that headspace of a world.
You know, of online and gaming and all that.
It's weird.
Will you ever play older versions?
Probably the only version I'll play that is old is going to be 1.0.
I know I keep saying it, but it's going to happen at some point.
Just for fun.
But I'm not going to play like 1.6.17 or whatever the hell.
You know?
Because there's like a million versions.
Because I think it could be fun to see what 1.0 looks like.
Don't do that.
It's depressing.
Don't tell me what to do.
I will make it not depressing.
You'll see.
It'll be all happy and jolly.
I have played a little bit of No Man's Sky Slavov.
But it's been a long time since I did that.
And the game has apparently changed a lot.
Like, it's completely different from launch now.
There was a lot of drama about it when it launched.
But now it's apparently good.
So.
But it did seem a little arcade-y to me, you know?
I do prefer games that are a little more realistic or rooted in hard sci-fi.
Like Elite Dangerous, at least.
So I don't know if I'll vibe with it.
We'll have to see.
I'll check it out one day.
I've not played Progamata.
Okay, I just want to get going, honestly.
I want to play Minecraft.
I don't even remember what I did last time.
Yeah.
Imagine if I never came back and that was that.
For like four hours.
I never said anything.
That was that.
I'm gone.
That would be so dumb.
Put that cookie down, it says.
Oh, there's sound.
Okay.
The New Dawn.
It's getting to be kind of old at this point.
Can I rename a world?
Edit?
No, probably not.
Let's not do that.
Let's see what I did.
Something with trains.
Right?
Oh, no.
That's what I didn't do.
I was going to do trains, but then I got distracted by a million other things.
Oh, thank you, past me.
Look at this clean inventory, man.
And potatoes as well.
Man, that's so nice.
It's like coming home from work and seeing that your son has, you know, cleaned the entire house and taking out the trash and all that.
Not that I would know what that feels like, but it feels like it, you know what I mean?
It's nice.
What's in here?
What's that doing there?
I feel like I will forget that this is in here.
Okay, whatever.
Guys, today we're going back to basics.
Because I think, yeah, I just need to gather more stuff.
And for that to happen, I want to go to the end.
Because I also want to kill the dragon.
I lost all my levels last time from falling into the pit right here.
So that's kind of bad.
But before I do, maybe I'll take another quick stab at the train situation.
Honestly, I don't even remember what I did last time.
Oh, I made this track out here.
That's right.
I also have a...
I have an engine somewhere.
I made a portable engine, but that needs coal and stuff.
Probably going to be useful for the train.
Then again, steam engine sounds like a train thing, doesn't it?
That's what trains were running on back in the day.
You put in some stuff, you make it hot, you boil some water, you get steam, and you make hams.
This kind of looks like a train, doesn't it?
Am I crazy?
Doesn't this look like a train?
I know it's not.
It says practice frog port, but it looks like a train to me.
That kind of looks like a train too.
But like a weird old version of a train.
But I know it's not a train, you know?
Did I ever try the spout?
I don't think I did.
Steam engine.
This is the one I need.
1024 RPM.
Up to 65,000...
...spin units?
Maybe?
Oh.
Was that an enderman?
Oh, wait.
It's my farm.
Oh, yeah, right.
I made this so big.
Look at this.
What the hell is this?
Get that out of there.
What a...
Oh, yeah.
It's coming back to me.
This is so amazing.
And then this thing is gonna get delivered here.
I love that.
And I have infinite food now.
Oh, and my wall down here.
Oh, I've been doing so well.
Good job, me.
So proud of myself.
Now, I kind of want to cover up this side, or at least the box, with maybe a little flapjack.
But let's not do that yet.
I need to see my situation here.
I got eight enderpearls.
I think you need...
10.
Or like...
12 or 16-ish.
It's more than eight.
So we're gonna have to go kill some endermen.
I guess the best place to find them is in the nether.
I have no gold right now.
I also should get ready for the nether with some potions.
There we go.
Potion of fire resistance.
I can even make more.
Oh, I need redstone dust for that.
Give me like half.
What's this say?
Oh, I did this already!
Nailed it.
Oh, actually, even better.
Oh, I can't...
Control-C?
That's terrible.
Oh, well.
Windmill...
Make it.
And...
Yes.
The path outside the house isn't complete yet.
You forgot the other side.
This one isn't done yet.
This one I'm working on.
Kidnap...
Yeah, this...
Dude.
Maybe we go through the nether and find a whole new area to explore.
Money not spend is money saved.
That's true.
Don't worry about this one.
Don't look at it.
Now, nether wart.
One, two, three water bottles.
A magma cream.
And one dust.
That's all you need.
Oh, and a power source, of course.
There we go.
Maybe I shouldn't carry around these pearls.
Kind of want to put a little funnel on top.
Or, uh, what's the word?
Hopper.
Let's make that a little nicer.
Awkward.
Now we do magma cream.
Am I ready with the rest, though?
We got the bow?
Check.
Oh, gold armor.
Right.
Gold armor.
Oh, that's a nice helmet.
It's beautiful.
I'm going to put this helmet in here.
Yep.
And now we put in the redstone dust.
Extend the duration.
Oh, and we need wood.
More than that.
Always good to have some wood.
Sixteen.
Lovely.
Now, potatoes are not actually the best thing I can bring.
It's kind of bad, actually.
Let's go farm some animals.
Oh, I don't even have that many.
We're going to have to let these guys multiply.
Before the slaughter happens.
I wonder if there's a block in create that lets me sort of, um...
weigh these animals.
So imagine you have, like, a...
like, a measuring plate all over here.
So when the weight reaches a certain threshold, meaning there are certain amounts of animals in here, then the slicing starts happening, you know?
Just a, uh, taut, metallic wire that's going across like this.
They all get sliced in half, right?
Or at least just the adults.
The kids will survive because the wire is above them.
And then when the weight reaches this threshold again, the wire goes again, you know?
Think about it.
The hell!
Good thing I heard that!
How come I can hear the creeper?
Aren't they supposed to be creeping?
That just saved my ass that I could hear that.
Okay, and potions?
We got it.
Uh...
Wonderful.
You go back in there.
Other than that, I think I'm ready.
Maybe a bed.
Ah, wait!
Nether?
We don't bring beds to Nether.
That's a mistake.
We do bring a shield, though.
Yes.
I think the rest is good.
So apparently you can also put trains in the nether and have them connect to, uh...
to the normal world.
So I'm very excited about that.
Are we good?
Bow?
Arrows?
Oh, I need some kind of ascension block.
Give me this.
Okay, off I go.
Let's go hunt some endermen.
Up!
Oh god.
Stay away from me.
I'm drinking my...
drink.
We came to the wrong dimension.
Now, where have I not gone in here?
I think that way I haven't, but...
It's kind of a shitty way, isn't it?
It's very hostile terrain.
I should actually drink this now.
Littering...
In the dimension.
Like, I don't like this, but, you know...
It is what it is.
We have to go this way.
I have a good feeling about it.
Hey!
There you go.
Let's just keep...
Oh!
Let's not forget torches everywhere.
I am immune to lava right now.
Oh!
Oh, that's bad.
Okay, this path sucks.
But does it, though?
Let's keep...
Let's keep walking.
I'm going across like this.
Kind of nice knowing that I'm immune to fire.
We're gonna do a...
Kind of a crooked straight-line Johnson.
Non-linear straight-line Johnson.
Okay.
I changed my mind.
I hate this.
Absolutely terrible biome.
This is direct from hell itself.
Let's just go that way.
Surely that's gonna be better.
Oh, wait.
I'm going the wrong way here.
There's my portal.
No, I went that way already.
That's the...
That's the fortress.
This way.
We're gonna go straight this way now.
That seems good.
I think I've already gone this way.
Which is technically north.
So we're going west now.
Okay, I went a little this way before.
But not that far, I think.
Yeah, this looks nice.
Part of me wants to collect experience, but if I'm gonna kill the dragon...
And hold on!
Maybe I can finally try to respawn the dragon.
I've never done that.
And I don't remember what I need to do to do it.
Something tells me I have been told this...
In one of the streams, but I honestly don't remember.
Something with the egg, obviously.
Well, this is some crap right here.
Why is this nether portal so bad?
Like, there's almost nothing I can do here.
I guess I could SLJ.
You know what?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
I believe.
Oh, there you are!
Oh my god.
Stay mad.
Oh yeah, and then if you go sideways, it's kind of faster, I think.
There you go.
Optimal speed achieved.
No!
Thank god it didn't shoot at me.
Could have destroyed the bridge and killed me.
Oh
wait, am I gonna have enough?
Oh, barely.
Nice.
Clean.
Dude, aren't there usually like a million endermen in the nether?
I feel like I'm so unlucky right now.
Oh, I can just walk down here.
Oh shit!
What do you want?
Okay.
Piss off.
I don't like...
Oh wait, let's go down here?
I really should just be exploring as well, just to see if I can find another fortress or something.
Whoa!
I hit the fire.
Again!
Not my intent...
Oh god, he disappeared.
I'm too good at the game, and I actually backfired that I was so good.
How long do I have left?
Two minutes.
Oh!
Here we go!
Oh, it looked like a tower or something!
I got bamboozled by the...
nature.
Okay.
Suck on that.
Dude, I don't like this path at all.
It's gonna be hell to get home.
But I don't have a choice.
Oh!
Wait, which one was that?
Nether?
Oh!
Explore all nether biomes.
So, wait, this is a new biome?
What's new about this?
Oh, nice.
Yep.
Oh my god, I'm so good.
Oh, wait, I need to put these torches in a way where I can...
see them.
Ah, eating another one.
Oi!
Damn.
Oh, I need to eat another fire protection.
Right now.
Let's, uh...
Hold on.
Let me see what's around here.
Oh!
I thought I was falling!
It's...
The particles made me think I was falling.
It's like relativity.
You know?
It moved up, so I thought I went down.
It's like when you're in a train and you're sitting still, but you think you're moving, because the other...
Oh, here we go!
Look at this!
Here we go!
Let's see what treasures we can find in here.
Oh, you're stuck, are you, step ghost?
That's too bad.
I need some, uh...
protection.
Give me this.
Those were the days.
Not sure which days you're speaking of here, but...
They sure were the days.
Those.
Okay, we got ascension.
Now, we gotta be careful, because this is some dangerous shit.
There's enemies in here?
With the black armor?
They are nuts.
Oh, wait.
I'm immune to fire.
But I'm not gonna be immune.
For a long time.
Do you mind?
Wait, what is this?
Where's all the treasure chests?
You know what?
Maybe I'll leave this behind.
It's kind of dangerous to do anyway.
Can I see any...
gold?
We have a bad guy up there?
Am I burning?
Yeah, there they are.
Oh, that's scary.
I can't do it.
I'm puzzling out.
Those guys...
They're actually gonna two-shot me.
I'm playing it safe.
Also, I haven't seen a single enderman.
And this is the whole reason I'm here.
Maybe the best way to find them is to just go into the normal world.
Okay, fine.
I'm gonna collect this.
Dude, I had a bit of a lock-on issue there.
Keep putting torches.
I'll put one up here.
Also, I only have 31 left.
Oh, wait.
I should have brought obsidian.
Crap.
Oh.
How do I get out?
I have to go back again.
Unless we find another portal in here.
Just randomly.
Oh, dude.
Let's try and find netherite.
I bet there's something crazy you can build with that.
But, I mean, that's gonna take a little, you know?
I'm gonna make a little SLJ here.
Just a bit.
We're gonna see what happens.
Because I need to go this way anyway.
That's just icing on the cake right there.
Oh.
Oh, wait.
Is that...
Mommy.
Check your banquet?
Oh, my God.
Nope.
We're gonna play this so safe.
SLJ stops at nothing.
Okay.
SLJ is not optimal right now.
Hey, guys.
What's going on?
Don't mind me.
Don't mind...
Get out of the way.
There we go.
We're safe now, I think.
Yeah, let me just do this.
I'm not sure.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Fuck.
I thought I was dead.
Wait, I'm gonna do this.
In case they come from behind.
I got them.
Oh, they're angry.
Look at this.
I see them.
What's up, dude?
Suck on that.
Can you hit me?
Got them.
Holy crap.
I don't want them to slice my angles!
What's that sound?
Oh, I ran out of blocks.
I have to go back.
Give me this.
Oh, wait.
I have these now.
Oh, yeah.
Of course.
Sorry.
I don't trust you, little guy.
Oh, man.
That gave me a proper fright.
No ankle slicing will happen today.
Whoa.
I will murder your children!
We're safe.
Oh, my God.
This is a perilous path I've taken here.
This looks clean-ish.
Unless they're gonna come flying from the sky.
It's gonna be very not good.
Okay, I like this land.
This land is good.
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
I want that gold.
I want to give gold to the pigs.
We're going for the gold.
Oh!
Fuck off!
Oh, man.
I was so afraid of what was behind me.
Okay, I think we're good.
The thing is, though, if I take this gold, they're gonna be angry.
What the hell is this?
Oh, quartz.
Oh, that's a lot of gold.
Oh, yeah.
That's nice.
Damn.
That's actually so helpful.
I think I was lacking gold at home anyway.
Okay.
Let's remember where I came from.
Um.
I don't know.
Are you angry now since I took the gold?
We pals?
We're pals.
Okay.
So I came from here.
Oh!
Oh, right.
This way.
Good.
And we're back.
Nice.
Operation Steal the Gold.
Successful.
I got no fire resistance right now?
I'm going over...
I feel like I should save my potions a little bit here.
SLJ for life.
Why is it so slow?
There we go.
Wait, that's not SLJ.
That's...
Barely...
Oh my god.
Come on.
Oh, that's nice.
Look at this.
Sweet.
Kind of just want to go down.
From here.
But getting back up is going to be a little problematic.
Wow.
Look at that.
Oh, there's lava right below me.
Let's keep going a little further.
I see more back here.
There we go.
Dude, if I die now, it's going to be so catastrophic.
You know what?
I'll...
No, I'm going to save my potions.
Fixed.
That could have gone the wrong way there, for sure.
Oh!
I'm sorry!
SLJ demands I destroy it.
Enderman!
Finally.
Let's get down.
Okay, I like this.
Obviously, we got to get back up there, so...
We got to make, like, a little...
What is the best way to do this?
Does it go up like this?
The hell?!
Cheating.
There we go.
It is fixed.
Okay.
Now, where was this guy?
That was too slow.
Shit!
Dude, I feel like there's more Endermen in the real world.
This is...
Oh, there's lava now, too.
Oh!
Portal!
No fucking way!
Let's go.
It's my ticket out of here.
And maybe we can, you know, adopt the mansion.
Good enough.
Not afraid of you.
Give me a cream.
Dude, this was the cleanest kill of one of these guys ever.
Now, the question is...
Do we have enough obsidian here?
I don't think so.
Oh, wait!
Are you gonna be angry if I loot this?
They may get angry.
Wait, I have an idea.
Hey, guys!
You want gold, right?
It's not you.
It's the other kind.
Where are you?
There you...
Oh, there you are.
Look what I got for you.
Have at it!
These guys can drop pearls now!
Meats?
Or...
Or bricks, I guess.
Oh!
Obsidian!
Yo, I need that!
Hold on.
Uh...
I don't know why they're going crazy, but...
Uh, okay.
They're going a little crazy right now.
I will litter everywhere.
Yeah, that's good.
Oh, I didn't mean to pick that...
Oh, sorry.
Here.
He gave me an eye, look!
I have four of them now!
Dude, this...
Fuck the enderman.
This is the way to do it!
It's like the optimal way.
And they also drop arrows as well.
This is fantastic.
I forgot how good this is.
Thank you.
Oh, wait.
I had an obsidian already.
Oh, no.
That's crying obsidian.
And then again.
Maybe that's also used for something.
No, it doesn't look like it.
Ew.
Enderman.
Uh, I will actually kill you.
Good night.
Come at me.
This is efficiency, people.
This guy is giving me pearls while I'm getting pearls myself.
Where did you go?
Oh, he can't find his way to me.
Okay, now I angered him.
Oh, wow!
Damn.
You came out of nowhere, didn't you?
Sweet.
Let me see what you got for me.
A potion!
Of water.
Okay.
Hey, you did- You left some gold behind.
Hey, we're not done here.
You need to go-
There you are.
What?
Didn't even drop anything.
Dude, there's enderman everywhere now, for some reason.
The hell?
Maybe when you kill one of them, they get angry and they spawn more.
I will kill your whole family.
Nobody survives this ordeal.
What?
Not a single pearl from these guys.
Where did my guy go?
Oh, he's up there.
Hey, look what I have.
I have something for you here.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't go anywhere.
Enjoy that.
Maybe you have a friend somewhere that can also help me out?
Oh, it doesn't look like it.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
Hap!
Oh, my God.
Did you see that?
Skills.
Almost 30.
Now, what have you given me?
Okay.
More obsidian.
That is wonderful.
And while you do that, I'm just gonna go ahead and grab this.
Soul speed 2.
That's nice.
I think if I destroy this gold, they're gonna get angry.
So, I'm gonna do it on my way out.
Calm down.
It's over here.
I didn't take it.
It's right there.
Now, I do want to fill up these boxes here, but I'm afraid that if I open them, they're gonna go crazy.
Remember when I opened some boxes in the past?
They went nuts.
Let's see.
Okay.
It doesn't look like they have an issue with it yet.
Yeah.
That's good.
Let's see what he's doing up here.
Some string.
Okay.
These water bottles, I'm not really intrigued by.
Here, I got more.
Man, I got like four pearls and then nothing for a long time.
Okay.
While you're doing that, I'm gonna go complete this portal.
We don't want the crying obsidian.
Oh, we're actually there.
Hey!
There it is!
I'll be taking something...
Oh.
Silk touch on that one.
Protection form?
You're gonna be mad at me?
You're not mad at me.
What if I do this, though?
Oh, shit!
Oh, no!
Are they angry?
They're angry now!
Uh-oh!
Wait, uh...
Here!
Look at this!
Look what I got!
I got shinies!
Yeah, check it out!
Everything's fine!
Sweet!
Thank you!
Now, what about some pearls?
Got any more of those?
I wonder if he's gonna go back to neutral after a while, after I've given him some gold, you know?
So we're friends now?
I don't want bricks.
I kind of want to find more like, all at once, you know?
I want to find, like, a bunch.
But let's just leave and see what happens.
Wait, I need a thingy to open.
Here we go.
See you, nerds!
I'm looking north, I think?
No fucking way!
What the heck, dude?
Okay.
That's crazy, yo.
Where's my food?
I'm blind!
There it is.
Hey.
Good night.
Trying to poison me.
Ow!
There's four of the spawners up there!
Yeah, but I...
I gotcha.
Well, this is kind of awesome, though.
I was wondering when I'd find one of these.
Fuck it.
I'm leaving it like...
I'm putting it like that.
There's one guy below me.
Aw, you fell down?
Oh!
Oh, it's you!
You little bastard!
Oh, he's off.
Why do they shoot so slow?
Oh, no!
I am in danger!
Just heal up.
Whew!
I don't have the good food, I only have potatoes.
That's actually a problem.
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
Aye!
Matey!
Let's see!
Hammer?
Yes?
Anything else?
That looks like it was it.
Okay.
What else can I plop in there?
Let's use this one.
Oh, it's almost full!
Oh, that's a disaster.
Maybe I don't need this gold chestplate.
Honestly, it's...
Let's put in bones.
I need more toolboxes.
That's what I need.
Hey!
Look at this!
Bunch of fire charges.
Water bucket.
I'll take that instead of my normal bucket.
And this is a way to get a bunch of copper if I need it.
Now, I do want to drink a potion so I can get better rewards here.
Potion of healing.
Let's get back up.
I think we're not done yet with these.
Oh, we are done.
Potatoes.
A key.
Nice.
And some bread.
But I don't really have space.
Oh, look at this bow, though!
Hey, that's actually a sick bow!
What's that?
A frosting cake.
Frosted cake?
That's what it looks like to me.
Don't need this.
Let's find a receptacle for it.
This is so cool.
It's been a while, man.
There we go.
What do we got?
More bow people.
Yeah, hit each other.
Dumbasses.
Oh, no!
I don't have a shield, dude!
I'm in big trouble.
I gotta make one.
Iron.
I think I have it.
I have it.
I got nuggets.
Turn nuggets in two.
You know what I mean.
Gimme!
Then we have wood.
Somewhere.
There.
Oh, yes, dude!
Easy.
Handle.
And we're back.
Funny thing is, I looked at that shield before I went on this trip and I thought, nah, maybe I should get a new one.
And I thought, nah.
Mistake.
God, I love...
Oh, but...
We don't have infinity on this one now.
Did I throw away my old bow?
What happened?
I don't know.
Not sure.
Did I actually throw that away?
There's no way I would do that, right?
Oh, my God.
Woo!
Nice.
I thought it was gone forever, but we're fine.
So I'm going this way first.
Let's do a little thing here.
Now, these places you can get lost in so easily, so I have to be careful.
What are you gonna spawn?
More bow people!
I don't like that!
Wait, what the...
We got little guys!
Ugh!
We're gonna die!
Just kidding.
It's no problem.
I'll get it all back.
I actually expected this.
It was part of my plan.
I'll prove it to you.
Right here.
I'll show you.
Right here on this page.
Yep.
37.
I die, and then heroically get it all back.
It's part of the script.
Did we leave any doors open?
We didn't.
Okay.
You're not gonna come in here, are you?
Good.
Alright.
Quick inventory?
Tell me I have diamonds.
Yeah.
No, it's not enough.
But I have sticks.
One of these.
You know what?
Let's make a sword.
Why not?
Let's just do that.
I got some armor here.
Helmet.
I feel like I need a bow.
I'll take some golden shoes.
Torches.
See, I should have brought a bit.
Damn.
Why didn't I think of that?
Now, food, of course.
I can make it on two whole chickens and seven pork chops.
I don't need more than that.
Because I'm gonna take it slow.
And other than that, I think...
I think we're good.
Yep.
Nothing else I need here.
I think.
I got the food.
Honestly, kind of a...
Oh!
Shield, dude!
Shield, shield, shield, shield.
There we go.
Now we're ready.
Let's go!
I'm even gonna keep the wood because it's nice to have.
Yeah.
It's no problem.
It wasn't even that far away.
This is gonna be the smoothest recovery of all time.
I'm conserving my energy.
And I put torches everywhere and I made sure that I had ladders, staircases, and SLJs along the way.
So it's not gonna be a problem.
Also, I'm an expert at navigating the nether.
The amount of times that I have gotten lost in here and then found my way back is...
is something you can count on, like, five hands.
Or less.
Five or less hands.
Let me go up here.
Give me this.
Small mistake there.
But it's fine.
I'm actually gonna make this easier for future me.
Uh, not the...
Okay.
Did you miss that?
How did you miss that?
I was point blank.
I believe I had an SLJ right here-ish.
No, I went down.
I went down.
That's right.
I remember.
Oh, and then I...
Uh, what did I do here?
I think I may have done some...
jumping.
Wait, shit.
No, here.
Yeah.
That's the way.
Don't mess with me.
You're really gonna follow me?
Okay.
Dude, they hurt.
Holy shit.
Ouch.
Wait, is my bow enchanted?
Why is it glowing?
Hello?
Oh, it is enchanted.
Unbreaking.
Oh, cool.
I think I did do a bit of jumping here.
Hiya!
Wonderful.
And now the next torch is over there.
Obstacle course, master.
Here we go.
Okay, I guess I did another crazy jump.
Hiya!
Yeah.
Yup.
Oh my god.
Flawless.
But how did I do this, then?
Maybe I just dropped down.
I just don't remember that.
Oh no, we got...
We got piggies!
Oh, right!
This!
Run!
Where's the entrance?
Shit!
This ain't it!
Oh no!
Get away!
What's happening?
Oh, there's pigs!
Dude!
How come I can't see the...
Oh, thank you, man!
Thank you!
You're a real bro!
Oh wait, it's over here!
It's over here!
Piss off!
Get up!
Wait for me!
Christ!
Should be over here...
Somewhere?
Dude, what?
Oh wait!
Maybe I just went through?
Is that what I did?
I just went like this?
I feel like I didn't do that, but...
Oh, I did do that!
I did!
Ah, right!
It's...
This is not the whole one!
That comes later!
Now we jump down.
Beautiful!
Boom, boom, boom!
Oh man, I lost all my levels though.
That's so sad.
I forgot about that.
Damn!
There is something we lose here.
Oh, I can't be sprinting too much.
Gotta conserve these pork chops.
And I went that way.
I did such a good job with these torches.
This is the result of many years, literally, of hard lessons learned in the nether.
Doesn't even take damage from lava.
I guess he's, um...
Born in the nether.
This is his natural habitat.
Okay, soon we're gonna go to another...
Uh, bastion.
And there's gonna be a tunnel through it.
And it should be completely safe.
Looks good.
Solid.
Down here.
Now, we have to retrieve our items.
As soon as we enter the portal, we're on a timer.
So, we have to...
be really precise here.
We can't mess this up.
Also, when we enter the portal, we're gonna trigger a bunch of spawners.
Because we're gonna be in that room and they're probably gonna be reset at this point.
So, we may have to just run from that and make a little wall behind us.
Oh!
Before I do anything, I'm gonna sleep there when I go through the portal.
And I'm also gonna grab some of this.
That should do it.
Okay, here we go!
Wish me luck.
Shit.
Okay, we're on a timer.
Um, you know what?
Actually, I can just...
It doesn't matter that I don't sleep.
I just need to right-click it and there we go.
Uh, let's go.
Let's go.
This way.
There they are!
Get it!
Inventory full.
Yes.
Throw that away.
That one.
This one.
Collection.
Sweet.
Get the rest.
Shovel.
Nice.
There's a shield there, too.
Dude, my inventory!
Nice.
Oh, toolbox.
Did we get both?
Let's see here.
We did get both.
Nice.
Dude, I think we're good!
We're back, baby!
That was scary.
Now we just continue on like nothing happened.
Because nothing did happen.
Nothing happened here.
Oh, there's money in there.
Okay.
Fuck this leather.
Don't care.
I also don't care about this blackstone.
The golden nuggets get turned into normal nuggets.
Oh, there's a chest right here.
Let's use that.
There's a cake!
A diamond and a block of iron.
Interesting.
Okay, I don't want this ghast here.
Don't want that.
Okay, now I go grab that.
Throw away the stuff we don't want.
And this goes away.
Can I eat this?
How do you eat this?
Is it because I'm...
Oh!
Wait, how do you actually...
Wait, how do you eat from the cake?
Oh my god.
I don't understand the mechanics behind the cake.
It's a mystery to me.
You know, I don't need a furnace.
Or this.
Wait, where's my crank?
Oh!
I brought a mechanical saw but not a crank.
That's a mistake.
I don't want that either.
I don't know what to put in here, man.
I'm running out of space.
Maybe bones.
I'm gonna get more, right?
And I can't be...
arsed.
So keep dropping them.
What's this bow?
Oh.
Maybe I don't...
care about this one.
Yeah, that's good.
Let's go kill them.
Let's make it that sound.
Is it the little...
guys on the floor?
Are you the one?
It is.
No problem.
Okay.
Taters.
Oh!
There we go.
And bread.
Okay.
I was hoping for more keys but, you know.
It is what it is.
Right.
So I came from down there.
Let's do this systematically now.
Let's stay on the bottom floor.
And keep walking.
Here we go.
Come at me then.
They shoot very slow compared to normal skeletons.
Missed.
Another key for me.
That's three now.
Now I need to find one of those that eats them.
Come here.
Gonna spawn again.
Another key.
Nice.
That got a little hairy.
But I made it.
Okay.
Now.
I'm lost already.
Where the hell did I come from?
I came from here.
There's stuff below me as well.
Man, this is...
These places are just impossible to find your way around.
Fire charge.
I wonder if I use a fire charge in one of those wind dudes if they just die.
I know that sounds super random, but...
Who knows?
Maybe it's true.
Running really low on food.
Ah!
Here we go.
Eat it!
Okay.
I mean, sure.
I'll take that.
Not fantastic or anything, but...
You know.
Throw this away.
Anyone else wants to eat?
Money!
I'm ready for the villagers.
I don't know what to throw away.
I want to keep everything I have.
Also, where's my other box?
Don't tell me I left that somewhere.
Oh, no!
Where's my other box?
It's gone.
Whoops.
That's gone.
God damn it.
It's probably gone now.
Like, there's no way I get that back.
I have no idea where I could have left it.
Maybe I never did pick it up from the initial recovery.
No, I did.
I checked.
Weird.
What did I have in there?
I don't think it was anything important.
So, there's that.
I guess I had one diamond in there.
I do remember that.
Okay, I still have a couple keys, though, I want to use.
Go back.
Oh, there's a key up there!
I didn't grab it.
Ah!
Ah, thank...
God!
Look at that, look at that.
I got it.
What's in it?
Let's put some arrows in.
And some bones.
No, bones I have on the other one.
Let's put wind charges in.
Maybe...
Do I even want these?
Yeah, I do.
Of course I do.
And the last one, maybe breeze rods.
Sounds good.
Very nice to find that.
Let me actually pick stuff like this up.
In case it unlocked something, it didn't.
Still didn't.
It's good to check, though, right?
Now with create, you don't know what you're gonna find.
Oh!
Pottery shirt!
I do want to collect those.
I want to make a collection.
I think I saw a door.
There.
Ooh, honey!
Do you want that?
Wait, I just picked up the decorated part like that.
I thought I broke it.
Ooh!
Would you look at that?
What a nice little upgrade.
Oh my god!
And a key as well?
These things are amazing.
Oh, wait!
I picked them up when I used my torch on them.
Oh!
And the pearls!
I think we actually have enough now.
Oh, wait!
I just realized what's happening, guys.
When I use my axe on them, I'm literally breaking them.
That's why I'm getting bricks.
I was like, why didn't I get any bricks for so long?
But that's why.
Interesting.
Why is it...
Hmm.
I don't like that.
Hold on.
Break it.
Well, I can't be carrying around these shirts.
It's gonna...
I'm gonna run out of space very fast.
Let's look for more doors.
Oh, maybe also these are gonna be important for something.
What about these types?
Nope.
Okay.
I came from there.
Now, these places are always bigger than they look, so...
There's no way I'm done in here.
Also, we are gonna go to the surface.
We got an eater.
Look what I got for you.
A book.
Efficiency three is actually amazing!
Sweet.
Oh, no.
Ow.
I don't think I wanted the last one anyway.
Am I double stacking things?
Gold here?
I think we're good.
This seems like a waste, doesn't it?
I feel like Indiana Jones.
That was my last pork chop.
Now I only have potatoes.
There we go.
This is Fight Club.
Right, I can't shoot them with bows.
I can't anger too many at the same time, though.
Maybe it's fine.
Hello?
Come here.
Oh my god, dude.
Fuck me, you're annoying.
Dude!
It's like a boss!
Get poisoned and shit!
Oh my god!
It's the gym boss!
Why is it so difficult?
I got you now.
That was just one.
I'm cooked.
Just avoidance.
Avoidance.
Yeah!
Ah!
There we go.
Next!
We have done it.
I'm gonna step on a pot.
Wait, what a weird-looking room.
Snowballs.
Oh!
Oh my god!
That music came in like a truck.
What is it gonna be?
No problem.
I'll eat you guys for breakfast.
Dude, I nailed that.
I need more people that eat things, though.
Oh.
Here we go.
Another book!
Riptide!
I think that was for the tripod, right?
Yeah.
Has to be.
Okay, let's just...
Let's go to the side here.
Dude, I'm lacking ascension blocks.
Like, it's crazy.
I can't get across.
Oh my goodness!
Come on!
You're not gonna spawn one more?
Oh, that was probably the last.
Power one.
No thanks.
Where are you?
Are you downstairs?
Huh?
Where the hell did you go?
Uh...
No!
I needed that!
I don't know where this guy is.
What is happening here?
Where did you go?
You're not up there.
You're down here?
Aha!
There's a whole other layer.
Oh my god.
There we go!
Oh!
Beautiful.
I see people who wanna eat.
Oh wait, this one already did, right?
You're not gonna eat again?
Nah.
Oh, wait!
We got a big guy down there!
But that means we gotta use the potion!
That I don't have.
That's too bad.
I would love to do that.
Yeah, I don't got nothing like that.
I think I also had some arrows in here.
Nice.
Man, I've had enough of this place!
Let's get out!
We're gonna just dig out.
I'm digging this way.
I hear lava though.
Maybe not smart to dig here.
I predict day.
I'm gonna have a flawless series of predictions today.
It's gonna be like staring into the sun.
With no sunglasses.
That's how bright it's gonna be.
I also predict, and this is a bold one.
And you gotta applaud me for having the guts to do this.
But I predict we're gonna find...
a hotel.
When we get up here.
Wait, we actually made it into another part of this?
Did I explore this?
Wait, this is new!
Hold on.
We're checking it out.
Man, I keep picking up this shitty bow.
Get away from me!
Okay, we're not leaving yet.
What's that?
Oh, music!
Ooh, let's actually grab that.
I don't want this.
Huh?
Cloud Skipper.
Mysterious conversion.
So I gotta do something to it, but we don't know what it is.
Interesting.
We'll figure that out.
Nice.
Another pearl.
Just randomly like that.
Hey, look!
Glass!
I broke it.
Ah, we got another big boy consumer.
Honeycomb!
Yo!
I feel like I need that.
What is that?
Whatever it is, I want to make it.
Even more honeycomb.
That's a funky looking block right there.
Let's get rid of...
Okay, it's not funky at all.
It's plain.
Big boy consumer.
No more...
Normal guys up here?
Maybe they're all hiding on the...
Bottom floors.
Let's go this way.
There we go.
Trim?
I mean, I did say I was gonna...
Do some trimming.
Golden carrots, though.
God, this inventory is just...
Horrible.
Wait, are we not stacking?
Oh, they're fire resistance!
Okay, you know what?
I don't care about these.
Okay, I don't care about the golden carrots.
They don't please me.
I'm very not pleased.
Okay, nothing back there.
Man.
I wish I had those potions.
Probably above me?
Oh, sh...
Zombies!
Finally, something other than archers.
Dude, expertly handled.
Holy shit.
And...
Some bread.
Okay.
I don't even want it.
How about that?
There's some good loot in these.
Go higher up.
There's no normal consumers anywhere.
And I have so many keys.
Let's all try to go this way.
Oh, wait.
I've been that way.
Well.
I think we are done here.
Unless we're not.
Let's keep exploring.
Yeah, this looks new.
Never mind.
Oh!
We got a guy up there.
But that's a big boy consumer.
BBC.
Like...
Oh, actually.
Hold on.
Is the game telling me something?
Should I use a compass?
It is a way to get home.
You know what?
Yes.
I'll take it.
I'm also gonna take one of these bets, actually.
The question is which one.
Which color do I like?
I like red.
And I don't care about these shirts.
I'm going shirtless.
Now we leave.
And I'm gonna leave right on top of this portal.
Or sort of on top of it.
Good luck following me.
I still say it's gonna be day, by the way.
And you'll see I'm right.
In fact, I bet...
Let me think of something big to bet on it.
So I can tell you how much I know.
How sure I am of what I'm saying.
I bet...
My dinner tonight on it.
If I don't get this right...
I will not eat dinner.
In fact...
If I get it right...
I also allow myself to buy a small bag of candy tonight.
That's right.
And if I get it wrong...
I will never, ever eat candy in my life again.
Now that's a bet, isn't it?
I'm gonna be right, though.
Because I have my ways of knowing.
Oh, shit.
Wow!
I forgot to keep...
I had to block for a second!
Thank God I did it in time!
Imagine I died.
I would actually cry.
Get ready for the sun.
Reset the controls...
Trolls...
For the sun.
Oh no, I messed it up.
It ain't pretty.
I did it again!
What's wrong with me right now?
Day, day, day, day, day.
I'm already...
I'm visualizing the candy.
And the dinner I'm gonna have.
You know how they say a man makes his own luck?
This is one of those cases.
Dude, how far down am I?
The fuck is this?
We seem to be in the desert.
Come on!
We're going through a thousand years of history right now.
These layers.
These stratas.
Oh, come on!
Yeah!
God, I'm good.
What a beautiful area, too.
So colorful.
Oh, look at that!
A little village up there.
That's a funky looking house.
I'm gonna steal that design.
I like the little, um...
Lock situation they have going on there.
Now, where's the hotel?
It's somewhere around here.
I'm telling you.
Maybe on the other side of this hill.
Get ready for it.
If there's a hotel on the other side of this hill, I will win infinite love and money tomorrow.
And she loves me.
Oh, they're teasing me.
Come on, show me.
No?
ODB!
Oh, wait, you're not ODB, but you're someone else.
But I kind of want to take you with me.
Ah, it's too late.
I don't have a lead.
And...
Hold on.
I didn't say how close it was going to be, but it's somewhere here.
I wonder if they can only spawn in certain biomes.
Now that I think about it, maybe that's the case.
Where have I seen them?
The hotels.
I guess I've seen them in the forest.
Mostly.
Maybe forested areas.
Ooh.
Hey, look at that hole over there.
Isn't that weirdly oval-shaped?
At least from this angle.
That looks nice.
I just want to dive into it.
You know?
God, I wish I could fly right now.
I need a Lutra.
So bad.
It's a whole new world.
What's that?
It's coal.
Dude, this is some hilly-ass terrain.
Wow.
I think we are far away from home right now.
And you know what?
I think we got everything we came here for.
Uh, let me see.
Wait, where's my pearls?
Oh, I thought I had more than seven, but I don't.
Okay, we're good.
We're good.
We're okay.
Uh, breeze rods, I think.
Yeah, put them in there.
Maybe just click things and see what happens.
You know, maybe they fit in there.
I can't be bothered to analyze.
Okay.
We're good.
Now, I think we should just head in the direction of the compass.
For now, at least.
Oh, we've got bandits on the loose.
Hey, wait!
They have potions for me!
The fuck?
They're zombies!
Unfair.
Did I get a potion?
You must have it.
An unbreaking crossbow.
Well, that's too bad.
I wanted to get a potion.
Ah, whatever.
Let's head home.
This was quite the adventure.
Died once.
But it's okay.
The first time doesn't count, you know.
Such are the rules of this game, of this land.
But now we're making our way home.
We've got the pearls.
We're gonna utilize them.
To find the portal that will take us to the dragon.
We shall slay it.
We shall respawn it.
And then...
We shall slay it.
We shall respawn it.
Somehow.
I still have to figure out how that works.
But I definitely need the egg.
100%.
And it will be glorious.
In fact, I don't even know how that looks like.
It's probably gonna be a sick animation or something.
I hope it's not just gonna be...
I do something with the egg and the dragon just appears.
You know, like, there's no animation.
It just sort of...
Pops into existence.
Like the mob spawning, you know.
When you get into range.
That would be sad.
What's this?
Red terracotta.
I kind of want to eat it.
Am I the only one who looks at this and goes...
Mmm.
I want to chew on it.
Looks like some kind of hard candy, you know.
But that is still kind of soft.
If you know what I mean.
It's one of those, uh...
Fake ones.
Like you bite into it and it's not actually a candy at all.
Some kind of chemical.
That you shouldn't have eaten in the first place.
But you want to eat them so bad, you know what I mean?
Like that, uh...
Teflon or whatever.
Love Teflon.
Wait, this is the weirdest mix of colors I've ever seen!
Look at this!
Isn't this really weird?
What is going on?
I'm gonna keep this in my bar.
And who knows?
Maybe we'll find a hotel on the way home.
Maybe I should be collecting stuff.
Oh, I can do something with the fan on it?
Oh wait, it's about to be night.
Go to sleep.
Don't want to risk any mobs out here.
We also got the subspace bubble.
Traveling, um, a certain distance in the nether.
I actually thought the achievement we got there was for discovering the trial chamber.
But it was actually because we traveled so far.
Hold on, I need to see something.
Acacia!
Maybe this is the biome where I saw the hotel.
That's right, I won the staring contest.
In fact...
I do be needing some food.
Don't mind if I slay you.
Nine raw bee from that, nice.
Yo, this whole area is kinda nuts.
The weirdest mix of biomes I've ever seen.
We've got desert over there.
We've got, uh...
Red Dead Redemption here.
Jungle there.
Acacia and oak here.
It's nuts, like, what is even happening?
No, that's jungle!
This is...
No, that's also jungle.
Yeah, it's all jungle.
Wouldn't surprise me if there was a swamp as well.
Somewhere nearby.
I need a boat, man.
Wait.
I have a boat!
Oh!
Sick!
Nice!
Wait, what happened to my axe?
What?
Oh, I put...
Oh.
I thought it got disappeared.
Whee!
Oh my god.
I get a tinkle in my tummy when I do this.
I know it's like a game, but I still get that feeling when you drop in first person in a video game.
Some games evoke that feeling, others don't, you know?
I think it's about the acceleration you experience while falling.
If it's done right, you know?
Oh man, that's treacherous terrain.
But...
Oh!
Wait!
We're gonna grab chocolate!
Coco!
We're gonna make chocolate flow.
I really wanna do that.
Let's grab some of that on the way home.
Look at this part up here.
Why does it look like that?
Why is the oak all moldy and rotten?
Hey, look, it's the same here.
What is wrong with these trees?
I've never seen that before.
Maybe it's part of create.
Oh well.
I kinda just wanna throw these shirts away.
Yeah, fuck them.
We don't need them right now.
Cactus, though!
How much do you wanna bet?
It's gonna unlock something crazy.
Alright, we can make colors, I guess.
And that's it, it seems.
Alright, boring.
Put them back.
I don't think I've ever gotten bamboo on this world.
This could also unlock something.
This is diametrium?
Or something similar?
Yeah!
Man, that was a nice jump.
Scaffolding?
Yes, as expected.
But, what else?
That's it.
Okay.
I'm gonna take a bunch.
Just like one stack or something.
Good enough for me.
Are we still going home?
We are.
Now, obviously, uh...
The compass is not gonna point exactly to where our home is.
But it should be close enough.
So that when I get close...
I should be able to find my way there.
Man, I...
I've forgotten how nice it is to just explore.
Oh, look at this here!
Oh, I thought it was money!
It's just, uh...
Vines.
It's a local pole.
Isn't that...
What vine is?
He used to do vines or something.
That's all I know.
What even happened to that platform?
Just sort of disappeared.
Uh...
Yeah, just go.
Oh, I get you!
Coco!
I almost forgot Coco!
I'm taking it with me.
I can't get over how much these look like lanterns.
Look at that!
Cookies and...
That's it?
All right.
I want more.
Oh, yeah.
Here we go.
Oh, that's a nice amount of Coco.
Does it grow on certain trees only?
I mean, in real life they do, but...
I got 15.
Maybe I can make them, uh...
Multiply.
Somehow.
Oh, look at this tree!
Oh, there's a big one!
Oh, my God!
Massive amounts.
Every time I'm in the jungle in Minecraft, I think of that...
Escape!
Radio show.
With, uh...
The man who would be king.
Or whatever.
Wasn't that...
And they talked about a jungle or something.
And the way they talked about the jungle...
Always makes me think of this.
I don't know why.
Just the cadence and stuff, you know.
I love that radio show.
You were hiding from me.
Okay, let's just grab one stack.
One full and nice, juicy stack.
58?
I can get a little more.
Here we go.
That's it.
We got it.
Man, I am really coming home with everything.
All kinds of exotic goods from far corners of the world.
This path reminds me of a memory lane.
Just a little bit.
I used to store a boat under a tree.
I remember that.
I'm kind of going backwards now.
But it's okay.
Okay, it's not okay anymore.
It's getting to be really not okay!
Can we turn?
180, please.
I'll go on foot.
No problem.
Gotta get some...
What do you call it?
Exercise, right?
Even though I heard, like, rowing...
It's some of the best exercise you can do, you know?
Same as swimming.
Apparently that also activates all your...
muscles and stuff.
And your glutes.
Bum bum bum, bum bum, bum bum, bum.
I should go to bed.
Sleep!
I'm still heading in the right direction.
Is that on fire?
We've got lava.
I'm gonna let it burn.
Oh, look!
The bamboo is burning and they go plop, plop.
It's like popcorn!
That's nice.
How come I can't plant corn?
I wanna have corn on the cob.
As they say.
With some...
salted butter on.
Even though I don't really like butter, I do like it on stuff like that.
I wonder how close I am to home.
So, I...
Since I got that achievement, I must be pretty far.
Or...
I was pretty far.
But it can't have been that far, right?
Guys!
I will be home within 30 minutes.
Mark my words.
No lost.
30 minutes.
Start the timer.
I'm trying to think what else I wanna bring back home while I'm out here.
Something you could only find in certain places.
Rare stuff.
So we have the pearls, which is gonna lead us to the portal, and we can...
That's already in the bag, pretty much.
Like, that one we got, right?
But other than that...
We already got jungle stuff.
Maybe we can find a swamp on the way.
And...
I don't know.
Pick up something specific to that biome.
I see a lot of bees.
I wonder if bees can only be in these oaky biomes.
Birch and oak.
I almost never see them anywhere else.
Okay, here's the open ocean.
I actually like when it's like this.
It's, like, super easy to navigate.
Wait a second.
Call me crazy, but I kinda...
recognize this.
Doesn't this look like the...
direction we went...
when we found the Danish cows?
Because we also had snow close by.
No, it can't be, though, right?
Because I'm coming from...
west.
I'm going east.
Am I not?
Wait.
Wait, how does that make sense?
I'm going west?
That doesn't make sense to me.
Because we went west...
leaving the base.
So we should be heading east to go home.
Maybe just trust the compass?
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe I didn't go west?
Weird.
That's weird, man.
I could have sworn I went west.
Then again...
Okay, so I went into the portal while I was looking north.
And then I turned left?
Yeah.
I went that way.
That's weird.
I don't want to say that the compass is broken, but...
Let's just say my nose has never been wrong when it comes to coordinates.
Tall boys!
This could be home.
Oh!
Wait, I really should be paying attention whether or not things are loading in actively.
Like, is my game lagging?
Because if it is, then...
Then it's new.
I feel like I recognize this village.
I've seen that village before.
That's...
That's one of my villages.
I made that.
I actually built that.
It does look kind of cozy, the way they have the houses set up in the snow.
The little chimneys and stuff.
How do they do the chimneys here?
Oh, I just can't see him.
Oh, there it is.
Okay, well...
My chimney that I made was better.
Their chimney is way too big.
What happened there?
Wait a second!
What is that?
We've got something up here.
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
What's going on here?
You little bastard!
Oh, shit.
Oh, okay.
Oh my god!
You hurt!
I can't die now.
Uh, go up.
Let me just sleep.
Just be safe here.
There we go.
Now we're safe.
I will go murder you.
And while I do that...
Maybe I'll cook this...
No!
I have an idea.
We're gonna go to this village.
We're gonna utilize their facilities.
Quick pit stop.
Because I just remembered I got rid of my oven.
We're gonna have a short rest here.
Please don't sink.
Shit!
God, I hate this!
It's the worst animation of all time!
How do people live here?
Who wants to live here, man?
Insane.
Okay, show me furnace.
I know you got it.
Large fern!
Ah, I broke it.
Ow!
Hey!
There we go.
Ah, that's nice.
Let's just sit here for a bit.
Fix the inventory.
Anything can go in here?
Nope.
Oh, something went in.
Nice.
That's what she said.
Is it the one I just...
I think that's the one I just opened.
Hell, we got a free slot now.
Let's put in...
This is done.
Dude, this may even be faster than the furnace.
You can do four at a time.
Let's put the...
Diamonds.
Good enough.
Sucks that we have one left over, huh?
Ha!
I copied this once.
For my other village that I made.
In season two.
And I...
I still may do it.
Because it looks so nice.
It was a geniusly simple design.
But so effective, you know?
Ah!
Dude, what the hell?
Oh my god.
How am I sinking?
I hate this mechanic so much.
It doesn't feel good.
No!
Get me the hell out of here.
Thank you.
Okay, we got meats now.
Is this...
This is the safe snow.
Shit!
How do I tell?
I can't tell.
You can't even tell.
I'm out.
Fuck this place.
Absolutely despise it.
I'm not gonna step on any of these.
Alright.
I will never make a village in the snow.
I just got reminded why I didn't do that, ever.
The only snow I want is asbestos snow.
Blown all over with a huge fan.
Just like in the old movies.
Look at that sunset, though.
We got freshly cooked steaks and a sun setting on the horizon.
What more do you want?
Oh, hello!
Oh, wait!
I've got bones!
I've got bones for you.
Somewhere.
Check it out, brother!
Become mine.
There it is!
We got more!
Friends!
There we go!
Come on, guys!
Oh, you're sitting.
There we go.
Now we have to go home.
But first we sleep.
Oh, no!
Did I leave my bed somewhere?
We gotta go back.
I hate to say it.
Come on, guys.
Okay, this name...
This guy's name is Billy.
We got Basso and Bruno.
BBB.
Don't step on the snow.
Okay, we should be fine.
Trust!
Don't panic!
Close your eyes!
It's fine.
Dude, the medicine is strong, even, at the same time!
Oh, I didn't mean to sleep, but okay.
Alright, we're leaving.
Come on, Billy, Basso, and Bruno.
We are out of this place.
We don't like snow, do we?
That's right.
Even the dogs know it.
Actually, are they dogs or wolves?
I'm not sure.
I mean, they're howling, right?
So they must be wolves.
Wild wolf in Philadelphia?
Is a movie that I saw once?
What the hell are you?
What is that?
It's a cat.
Why didn't it look like a cat?
Get him!
Come on!
Basso!
Get him!
Wait, he's running from them!
Come on!
Yeah!
That's how we do it.
Now, this is how you go hunting.
You bring hunting wolves.
Wait a minute.
I came to this land because I saw something I wanted to investigate.
I completely forgot about it.
I'm gonna go investigate.
There was something down here.
Something very odd looking.
Down this way.
Huh!
You hit Billy!
Come here.
I will slice you up into thin pieces of meat.
And serve them to my wolves.
Man, I don't like hearing the dog slash wolf go.
Well, when they get hit, it's heartbreaking.
We gotta give them some armor, actually.
I forgot how to make it.
But there is a way to do it.
This right here!
What is that?
Oh, it's like the underwater thing, but...
It's not underwater.
I actually have no idea what cursor vanishing is.
I don't know what that means.
I've never understood it.
I'll take this.
Why not?
I guess...
You know what?
Let's go fish for a bit.
Because surely there are some items that can be made with create that you can only do from fishing.
And I'm gonna go...
Oh, wait.
Are they gonna come with me?
Oh, this is gonna be a little...
Oh, no.
Yeah, just gotta make sure to do that once in a while.
Come on, guys.
Oh, no!
It's gonna be a problem.
How are we gonna do a voyage?
Okay, guys.
Just follow me.
We're going on land again.
I am bringing you home.
All three of you.
Bruno, Basso, and Billy.
We're gonna give them name tags.
Hey, look.
We can make these.
What?
Can we make some kind of jam or something?
There was a spout on that.
You saw that?
I'm bringing the berries.
Oh!
Fuck work.
Dude, my inventory is driving me crazy.
Fuck the taters.
I don't want...
You know what?
I don't want Riptide.
I said it.
It's up.
I've had enough.
I can't wait to get home and empty my inventory.
Wait a second.
What does it take to make...
Oh, God.
What was the name of it?
I can check.
Toolbox.
Yeah, that's not happening in the wild.
Absolutely not.
Or maybe it is.
No, it's not.
It ain't.
Maybe it is!
Wait.
It ain't.
We cannot do that in the wild.
Ooh, flowers.
No.
Don't be tempted by the flowers.
Is everyone with me?
Where's Bruno?
Ah, there you are.
Thought we lost one.
We're good, though.
So, basically, what I think the thing is over there, it's like the underwater thing just happened to be spawning, like, on land.
Because it's, like, close to the water and maybe there's some finicky stuff there.
Are we still heading home?
We are!
Man, we're right on the path.
Oh, I thought it was a tower.
I think I'll go up here and get a look.
I need to see if there's anything around me.
Dude, that looks kind of messed up over there.
Look at that!
Oh, it's because it's spawning in as I approach.
It looked like...
I don't know what it looked like, but something unnatural.
I want to see what's on this side.
I feel kind of safe having these wolves with me.
But they don't have armor.
So it's also kind of risky.
Yeah, I don't see anything exciting.
You know what that means?
River rafting!
I don't know why I did the Mario theme.
But this way.
Okay.
Come on, guys!
Follow me!
Oh, god.
I almost smashed your head.
Turned it into...
jelly.
Now, are you able to follow me?
Are we gonna have a problem?
That's right.
Teleport to me.
Are you following me here?
Not real.
Ow!
Come on.
You know what?
Maybe I shouldn't boat at all.
River rafting is for the weekend.
Anyway.
Everyone knows it.
Real men use their feet.
Hey, you!
The hell was that sound?
You heard that?
There's an animal here.
Oh.
It's a wolf.
No, it's a...
Dude, what's the name?
Fox!
Even in this game, the foxes sound weird.
Yeah.
I'm gonna grab some more of this.
I'm making jelly.
And then I will go to the farmer's market.
Or the state fair.
There's a name for that in America.
Where you go and you sell jelly and jam.
And you bring, like, carnival rides and stuff.
And there's, like, a petting zoo.
You know?
Never been to one of those.
But I would love to go to one of them.
More dogs!
Join my rebellion.
You're with me.
A whole army.
Nice.
Okay, so we got Audrey and Allie.
Add them to the mix.
Oh no, not the water.
How will we overcome this burden?
Get ready for quantum teleportation.
On my mark.
Three.
Two.
One.
Beautiful!
Oh shit, come on.
Let's go.
Follow me.
We're going towards the rising sun.
I mean, the setting sun.
But it sounded better with rising.
Audrey, Allie, Billy, Basso, and...
Bruto!
Let's see if we can find more dogs on the way.
That's a big hole.
Wish I had Elytra.
I would totally fly through that.
That seems like a far away dream right now.
Oh, look at that.
Look at the way it's setting over the horizon and those trees.
You got your dogs with you?
Is there anything else you need in life?
Dude, that...
Look at this!
That is amazing.
Let's go to bed.
Ah!
I fell.
Um...
This way.
And what is that over there?
Crime!
You see, I can spot crimes.
From so far away.
Even without the glass.
I saw it.
That's why I zoomed on it.
I saw something wasn't right.
Money!
You know what?
Yeah.
Let's go grab the money.
I do like that.
There's also cows we can slay.
Come on, guys!
Teleport!
Everyone's here.
Alright, you're gonna die.
Everyone dies.
I do wonder if I can feed them raw meat.
Will that make them happy?
Wait, are they gonna have children?
Oh my god!
I never thought about that!
Of course that would happen!
They must have adopted, though.
We gotta cook this meat.
Wait, wait, wait!
This is not what I saw.
Ha!
That's so much of it!
Look!
There's more!
We're rich!
Holy cannoli!
Have you ever seen anything like this?
We're grabbing this one up here first.
Dude, I've always wanted to try a cannoli.
I've never had one.
I don't even know what's in it.
Chocolate, I guess.
I hated that!
Everyone...
I guess that answers the old question of...
Would you follow me into anything blindly?
And you would.
Did I see even more money?
I'm gonna grab the remaining two, and then we're on our way.
Oh, no, come on.
Oh, there's more!
How did I miss that one?
Yo, why is there so much money here?
Did that give a lot of experience?
Okay, so I think it's...
Right here.
Yeah.
What is that?
It's a frog!
Frog!
Hmm.
I never did figure out what frogs eat, so I never could replicate them in the lab.
Maybe, uh, this time around, I'll manage to find out.
This gravel is annoying.
God, that's annoying.
I just want to scream.
By the way, doggos, some of you are expected to die on this trip.
Not everyone will survive it.
Swamp!
Wonderful!
Let's see what we can find here.
God, I need to...
Oh.
Oh, man.
Okay, who cares about fire charges?
Not me.
I don't care about these sticks either.
Or, you know what?
I don't care about the fire resistance.
I said it.
Both of them, gone.
Yep.
Off my hands.
And we're also going to throw away...
We don't need these keys!
Gone!
That was so brave of me.
I can't believe I did that.
A portal!
We shall...
We shall go have a gander at that.
I kind of want these.
We're going to put them on the lake.
We're going to make the lake next to our house, like...
Really nice.
Green and clean and...
You know, really...
Filled with life.
And then we're going to pollute it.
With pipes of industry.
That's the look I'm going for.
Jump!
A golden apple, you say?
Why not?
Don't really want anything else.
I just don't have room for it.
And I don't have enough obsidian to make that portal.
I say no.
I think I'm actually close to home.
Wait, I better be close to home.
I have, like, approximately two minutes left.
To find home.
Oh, shit.
We gotta go!
There's no way!
Come on, doggos!
Follow me on the lilypads!
Oh, shit!
You're not doing it!
Oh, no.
We're not going to make it!
I can't.
It's too deep.
I'm coming back.
Wait, they're somehow making it.
Look!
Oh, no.
Not the lightning.
This is not good.
Follow me.
I know a safe path through these wastes.
Whatever you do...
Billy, Basso, Bruno, Audrey, and Allie...
Do not follow the lights.
Okay?
We got incoming!
Bruno, you take left!
Billy!
That's it, Audrey.
We got this.
Teamwork.
Good job, good job.
Creeper on the right.
We don't deal with that.
We run.
What the fuck is going on here?
There's explosions everywhere.
It's like a war zone.
We may have to go to bed.
Sleep.
Right underneath the tree.
Quick!
Spider coming!
Protect me while I sleep.
I wonder if they do that.
There we go.
No problem.
Unfortunately, I didn't make it in 30 minutes.
It is what it is.
I overestimated my abilities.
My navigational skills are just not what they once were, you know?
Hey, we finally made it to the crimes, as much as we saw in the distance.
That's kind of nice looking.
Ew!
Dude, we got Beauty and the Beast here.
Look at that!
Let me see this compass.
I also got to start worrying about whether or not I'm overshooting my home.
You know?
Because that could really be a thing.
The fact that we're seeing this wood right here is a good indicator.
But at this point, I don't really know how far away I am.
I feel like I should be close, because I've been wandering for ages.
Give me your meat.
I think I actually did bring my crank, and then I left it somewhere.
Because I wouldn't just have a saw in my inventory and not a crank, right?
That doesn't seem right.
Wait, didn't I spawn in a swamp?
This could be it.
This may be the swamp.
Which means we are indeed coming from the east.
Which ain't good.
Actually, it is okay.
Because that means we're just going to go west, and we should be fine.
Sup, Fragos.
Dude, that's a huge mushroom!
Look at this one!
Have you ever seen one this big?
Damn!
Why is that one so big?
Yeah, this is like the max size I've ever seen.
Oh wait, jungle?
I don't know that!
I'm lost.
Oh no.
There shouldn't be any jungle here.
Wait, the compass is kind of reacting a little?
I need to just go on a straight...
Yeah, yeah, okay, we're actually kind of close.
The fact that the compass is twitching when I run in a straight line means we're actually close.
At least close to where I spawned.
But let's not forget, I did wander off for quite a while before I did find the place I decided to settle my land on.
Wait, this is it!
This is where I spawned!
It's like the weird Swamp 2.0.
Yeah, yeah, the penis!
Remember?
That's how we started this thing.
So, yeah, I still don't understand how we're coming from the east, but...
Usually I come from the west.
The...
What?
Mangrove roots.
Oh, man, I really...
Did I go west when I found my...
I must have gone west.
Well, I think we're...
Here?
It's right here!
This is it!
This is where I spawned!
And the penis was right here, I think.
And I made a joke, you know, and all that.
And then what did I do?
Let me see.
Okay.
So, I actually just followed the sun.
Yeah, we don't want to go to where the sun don't shine right now.
We're following it.
Oh!
Oh, no.
I'm actually...
There's a big chance I'm not gonna find where I am!
Because I honestly don't remember which way I went.
And I don't know if I went in one direction.
It's a big problem.
Just follow the sun.
It'll be fine.
Mert!
I need a, um...
Like, one of those anchors.
Respawn anchor.
I remember this coal?
I'm just kidding.
I don't remember that at all.
In fact, this acacia is not even on my mind.
Doo-doo-doo-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum.
I'm gonna kill these cows.
Bam, bam.
That was a village on the way!
Let's see if we can find it.
A torch!
Okay, this is it.
Has to be.
Doo-doo-doo-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum.
You see that cinematic pan?
No.
I think I know where I am.
And it fits, too, that this is sort of north-ish of where my home is.
I remember that boat!
That boat was to the east.
On the fifth day when I looked.
The way I was looking.
On that particular day.
And boy, was I looking.
I was looking!
My eyes were bulging.
They were popping out of my school.
I was ogling.
Is it oogling or ogling?
There's a word for staring that is...
like ogling.
That's what I was doing.
I was ogling to the east.
And boy, what I saw...
drove me wild.
I'm getting excited, because I'm close to home.
It's actually happening.
That doesn't ring a bell.
Wait, this may not be the same cows!
I can't go on a boat, though.
Then my herd is gonna die.
This is a problem.
I also don't have any food.
I'm gonna have to resort to berries.
I wonder if I can chain together boats.
Oh, but wait, I can have multiple boats, I guess.
And then put the docks in them.
That's the way to do it, right?
Okay, this last stretch...
Wait, I don't remember going over water, though.
It has to be this way.
I went on land.
There is one thing I do remember.
I saw two mountains that I decided to make a bridge between, and then I decided against it.
That was also the point at which I had to poop.
That's why I remember that so vividly.
I took a break at that time.
And you say my memory's bad.
Hello?
How would I remember that?
This may actually be one of the mountains.
Quick sleep before the monsters come.
Oh, we did get an achievement here.
Under lock and key.
We also got wax off.
Scrape wax off a...
Did I do that?
I don't remember doing that.
Oh, there is an achievement for stepping foot.
Okay, well, there we go.
This may be one of the mountains.
Am I still going...
Probably.
This feels right.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is it.
The two mountains, remember?
I think those are the two mountains.
The tale of two mountains.
Man, look how terrible these berries are.
I just ate, and I'm already at half food.
Berries suck, yo.
Yeah, I think this is the point.
Which means I'm actually super close.
Because I wandered only for maybe like three minutes after this, or five minutes.
And then I found it.
Okay, I gotta...
Oh my god, dude.
Oh, I can't be eating berries.
I actually refuse.
It's that bad.
And I don't have a furnace.
I'm going to walk.
That's a weird looking horse.
It has measles.
It's a sick horse right there.
Crime.
So I was up there, I'm pretty sure.
Stone.
It looked like it had layers.
Village.
This could be the village that I also explored.
God, I hope I'm actually even going the right way.
This could be completely off mark.
I could be going in a completely random direction.
I'm starting to doubt myself.
It's not good.
I'm on my last legs here, running on fumes.
Hey, hey, hey.
They have a furnace.
We're going to utilize their furnace and their facilities.
Up, up, up, up, up, up.
Terrible foundation for this house.
Oh, nice.
That'll do it.
I don't need a furnace anymore.
Guys, I'm cooked, dude!
This doesn't ring a bell at all!
Oh, fuck.
It's ogre.
Let me see.
Okay.
I mean...
Maybe we go to the Danish cows.
And take it from there.
I mean, it could just be another one.
And there's multiple, right?
Wait, let's walk a little bit more.
I have a feeling that maybe behind this mountain, everything's going to come together and it's going to be wonderful, you know?
There'll be snacks and drinks.
Some calm music.
Good times will be had by all.
We will put on some Diddy Kong racing, you know?
What is it, Jaggy?
Want to get up?
You can sit here if you want.
Look at how I slaughtered these cows.
You see these dogs I have here?
They're my friends.
I have so many of them.
Jaggy, what are you doing?
Sit down.
Why are you acting like this?
Maybe you can hear her purring.
He just purred into the mic.
Oh, now she's rubbing against the mic.
Oh, I'm sorry, doggos!
Are we fine?
I think we're okay.
Wait, who are you?
Oh, I thought it was a torch!
No!
I got baited.
I got nature baited.
Damn!
I just got so excited.
It was exhilarating my heart.
Jaggy.
I'm gonna have to use the lint roller after this.
I can tell that right now.
If you hear weird noises, it's Jaggy doing things with the mic!
Jaggy!
Jaggy, I need your energy.
Do you think there's a house that belongs to me on the other side of this mountain?
Oh, let me move this back.
And, you ready?
Guys?
Is this my home?
Yes or no?
Jaggy!
Oh my god, she's controlling the mouse.
Here we go.
And...
Shit!
I fell in the hole.
I will look at my home in six seconds.
And...
It's not my home!
I knew it.
I knew it wasn't.
You know why?
Because I saw this over there and I don't remember this at all.
But, you know...
Wait.
What's that?
Look at that!
Is that my home?
God damn it, Jaggy!
Dude, I have no idea where I am.
Where am I?
Jaggy wants to be...
famous.
Jaggy!
Calm down.
Did you just cry because I destroyed that?
I'm gonna eat the golden apple!
Ow!
Wait, I have golden...
I've never seen this before.
I have golden hearts now.
Jaggy!
There's gonna be cat hairs everywhere!
What is it?
Are you hungry?
Hold on.
You have plenty of food.
I think she just wants to play.
She also wants to play Minecraft.
I don't know if you can hear this.
She can't get any physically closer to the microphone right now.
Jaggy, I need you to tell me.
Do I go right or left?
Left, you say?
Okay.
We can do left.
What was that sound just now?
Sounded like a bunch of birds.
Flapping their wings.
Jaggy!
That was a good sleeping session.
Okay, come here.
You're gonna be right here instead.
Okay, okay.
You're gonna be right here.
No, okay.
My god, she's full of energy right now.
I gotta admit something, guys.
I don't even know which direction I'm going.
I'm just sort of going right now, which is the worst thing I can do.
Oh, man.
We may have to...
We may need a new home.
I legitimately don't see any way I can find my way home.
I fucked up.
I mean, obviously, I'm gonna keep looking for a little bit longer, but...
I can't believe this.
I broke the cardinal rule.
Don't get lost.
I got lost.
I didn't take the necessary safety precautions.
I did it willy-billy-basso, and it was a bad idea.
It was willy-billy-bad.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
That looks oddly familiar to me.
We may actually be here.
Oh, please don't cope myself.
Wait.
Guys.
Okay, you ready?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
Oh, we're gonna play a game of where's my home?
You wanna see my home?
My home is...
Hold on.
I'm not ready.
I'm gonna look in...
11 seconds.
I'm gonna pop the question.
Is that my home?
Wait, what?
Hold on.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, hold on.
Is that my home?
Is that my home, guys?
I think I see it.
I can hear it.
It's my home!
It was right there!
That's amazing!
You know how I knew I was home?
Because I...
I recognize crimes anywhere, okay?
I know my crimes.
I saw...
that!
And this stupid-ass structure...
has been annoying me every time I sail past it.
And I was like, oh, wait a minute.
That's north of my home.
So I knew it was somewhere south.
I mean, it's not a crime.
It's just disgusting, you know?
It's like when...
when someone in the supermarket...
asks, can I go in front?
You know, and then they take forever.
Not respecting your time.
And shitting on you letting them go before you.
With all their wares.
It's not illegal, but it's disgusting, right?
That's what that hill is.
Oh, we're back!
Dude, I was so close to starting over.
Imagine I made my home right next to my last home.
Jesus Christ.
And we made it home with everybody!
Billy, Basso, Bruno, Audrey, and Allie.
What's up, everybody?
Uh, you know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna make a little perimeter.
Audrey, you stay here.
Billy, you have your little perimeter over here you're gonna patrol.
Come on, Billy.
There you are.
You sit there.
Basso, I need you in this corner.
Right next to the portal.
There we go.
Yep.
Wait, hold on.
Audrey, I told you.
Audrey, come on.
Wait a minute.
They had a baby, didn't they?
We have a new one.
It's gonna be named, uh...
Hmm.
Amtrak.
Come here.
But first, Bruno, you are right there.
Amtrak.
Allie!
You're gonna come over here.
You're gonna protect the herd.
You're gonna be a sheep rustler.
There you go.
And there it is.
We now have a perimeter of doggos.
Protecting my shit.
God, that's so fast, the way that spins, man.
It's a butte, Clark.
It really is.
PTSD!
No, wait.
That's the other one.
OSD.
No, that's Operational System Directory.
I don't know what I'm saying, man.
Uh...
Oh, it's time to empty the inventory.
It's gonna be good.
In you go.
And fire resistance.
Oh, let's put that over here.
Fire resistance.
Oh, there we go.
Enderpearls!
This is all I needed.
I have 15 now, which means if it is 12 we need, we have three...
Three.
We have three to use.
And I will do it with three.
Can I do it with three?
That's a question I pose to you.
I can do it with three.
Because I'm gonna do some crazy shit.
I got 49 emeralds, by the way.
I am kinda rich.
I keep thinking these leathers are foods, but they're not.
Let's smoke those beefs.
Okay, leather is miscellaneous.
Decorated pot.
Let me decorate my house with that.
One there.
We're gonna have one in that corner.
Definitely one right there and one here.
What do you say to that?
Maybe one...
Two of them here.
Three pots!
Yeah, that's good.
These are my wishing pots.
I take a little note with a wish on it and I stuff it inside one of these pots and then when I go on an adventure the wish will come true.
And only when it comes true will I reveal what the wish was.
Otherwise, where's the fun in that?
Spider-Eye, I believe miscellaneous.
Now, cocoa beans.
Let me see here.
Coco!
Uh, oh.
Chocolate glazed berries!
Dude.
Oh, but we need chocolate for that.
Bar of chocolate!
Right.
Okay.
Nice.
Cookie.
Red glazed terracotta.
Uh, let me see here.
Bar.
Chocolate.
I'm assuming, what do you need to make chocolate?
Milk?
Assuming milk chocolate.
Sugar.
And bread?
Right?
That's how you make chocolate.
Or, no, what not bread?
Wheat.
And what else do you need?
Oh, wait.
Am I thinking of cookies?
Oh, almost.
But I think we need milk.
Let's make a cookie.
Wheat and cocoa beans.
Wheat.
I have wheat.
only five.
But look, look at this.
Oh, we got a lot now because automatic wheat collection is happening.
Mm-hmm.
Cookie.
Let's make 16 cookies.
Dude, I'm actually gonna eat cookies for dinner in this game right now.
This is the reward I get for making it home after being lost.
There's no mom to stop me.
That's it.
We are now full on cookies.
That's amazing.
I wonder if I can put them, like...
So, there's also a table cover, right?
I wanna put the cookies on a table.
Table cover.
Oh, here we go.
Come on.
If that isn't amazing, you come in here and you smell the freshly baked cookies.
I kinda wanna put more.
Can I put more?
I mean...
I guess it's like a hot plate now.
It's gonna stay hot.
Because, uh, the smoker.
Right?
And then I eat the last cookie.
Oh, I don't have one in my ass.
Stomach.
Bread and wheat.
Now, berries.
Berries, berries, berries.
Glowberries.
Oh, you...
Ha!
You can haunt normal berries to make glowberries.
Interesting.
Alright.
I'm gonna fix this inventory now.
And we also have these two.
We're gonna put them down.
Lots of arrows and stuff.
Dude!
I have so many arrows.
I guess I got them from the pots in the trial chamber.
I think breeze rods belong in here.
Bamboo is definitely green.
Magma cream.
Oh my god.
It feels so good to empty this inventory.
I can't tell you how good it feels.
so nice.
Another rack.
This is construction.
Now, we don't have any place to put this stuff.
I think we need some chests near the enchanting area.
Or even better.
Enchanted books.
Nah.
Here's a chest.
That's fine.
In fact, we can even put one like in here.
No, we can't.
Then we can't open it.
Oh, no.
I kind of like how that looks.
I'm not going to lie.
That looks kind of cool.
For now, at least.
In you go.
Cocoa beans.
That's food.
Same as that.
Dirt.
And I got leftover books.
I got leftover books.
Clean.
Put
everything in here.
Did I leave my crank at home?
Oh, I did.
Okay.
Nice.
Let's put that in here where it belongs.
This helmet is also kind of weird.
Oh!
My helmet broke?
Now I have three diamonds so I can make another pickaxe.
Because mine is about to expire.
And soon we're going to be level 30 because I'm going to kill the dragon.
Now, we got this music disc.
I feel like I should make a music disc player.
Jukebox.
Requires a diamond.
Okay.
Let's do it.
I'm fine with that.
So apparently we can do something to it and create a new disc.
Wait, which one did I need to...
Hold on.
That's a little loud for me.
That literally changed nothing.
That's crazy.
There's no difference.
Maybe slightly?
Wild.
Hold on.
Let's...
One.
That's one?
Okay, so it is working.
That's insane.
There's something off with that slider, dude.
That's not right.
Wait, what?
Oh!
It's like any music disc.
Cloudskipper.
I gotta do something to it.
Is it related to this bell, I wonder?
Where is that bell?
Didn't I have a bell?
Oh, maybe it's in here.
Bell?
I don't see a bell.
Hmm.
I must have left it somewhere.
Anyway, finally clean inventory.
I'm gonna go fish now.
Certain things you can only find while fishing.
I think.
And I wanna try and see if I can unlock stuff with Create.
And then after that, we're gonna go to the end.
and kill ourselves a dragon.
It's good to be home, though.
Take this shit out.
There we go.
Oh my god.
I'm fishing!
Where was I?
Right.
Cheers.
I'm so happy I made it home.
Oh!
Man, what a trip.
I was scared I would have to start over because there's literally no way I could have known which way to go.
Huh?
Oh, it's just...
Just catch a fish.
I thought I just got something important.
Hey, a puffer fish, I guess, is kind of important.
That's unique.
What I think Curse of Vanishing does
is there's just a chance that it gets broken on any use.
You know?
Like, when I pull in a fish or whenever I reel it in, there's a chance it just disappears.
Like, it's gone.
Poof!
Up in smoke.
And I won't know what happened.
But now I do.
Maybe.
I want to find some cats, too.
What the hell was that?
I thought I got a key.
I also just unlocked something new.
Oh, a trapped chest, I guess.
Or a tripped chest.
Tripwire chest?
No, a trapped chest.
I don't see when that is useful.
I mean, maybe in multiplayer.
But in single player, I don't see the use for that.
Because the bandits or the monsters, they don't really rummage in your chests, do they?
Maybe I fish up an amazing fishing rod.
There's a chance.
I do wonder, though, now.
So, when I fish, right, I technically right-click with an item.
So I'm thinking a deployer.
A horizontal deployer with a fishing rod?
Maybe it'll fish for me.
That's something to experiment with.
Maybe you can feed the fish in the lake and have them multiply just like normal animals.
What was that?
Oh, a bone.
What do fish even eat?
I guess other fish.
Ah, maybe greenery on the bottom.
Maybe some...
Kelp, actually.
I'm gonna enchant my fishing rod before I do that again.
When you're used to the fast fishing rod, you know it's kind of painful having the really slow one.
Only level 21, though.
Let me see here.
Oh, I guess I can't do it because it's cursed or something.
What do I need to make a fishing rod?
That makes so much sense.
Actually, I can make it.
There you go!
That actually kind of felt good.
Lock of the sea.
That's the one I want.
Level requirement, 24.
I wonder if I need more books here.
Oops, what did I just do?
Oh, there we go.
I think I need more books.
Oh, no.
I'm not gonna have enough.
Bookshelf.
Oh, my God!
Please spell!
There we go.
Three books for one bookshelf.
And to make a book...
Papers...
Okay.
I mean, I have leathers.
Papers.
It's kind of easy to make, too.
Sugar cane.
I need to make a sugar cane automator.
That one was super easy to do, even in normal Minecraft.
It's probably even easier here.
Let's
see.
What am I looking for?
I totally lost my train of thought.
I guess cardboard...
Can be used.
But, hold on.
If a cardboard can count as a paper...
No, it's the leather substitute.
It's not actually the paper substitute.
It's just because it was in the same spot as the paper.
Confused me a little bit.
Oh, this doesn't belong here.
Put you in there.
Again, we need to find the hotel.
Like, it's driving me crazy.
And I think what can really help with that...
Elytra.
Which means we gotta go to the end.
Which means...
End of pearl time.
I...
I need blaze powder for that.
Tell me I have enough.
I don't think so.
Damn, I forgot about this.
Oh, no.
Oh, crap.
Pearl.
Wait, really?
Oh, I have ender.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot about that.
Sweet.
Yeah, we gotta go back to the nether.
Should be easy, though.
There's a fortress right when I go in.
Stick.
Tripwire hook is redstone.
Yeah, okay.
I just need some gold.
If I have it.
Any gold?
Helmet.
I'll just keep this on me.
You know what, actually?
I'll take some gold with me into the nether.
And we need arrows.
30.
I want to give the pick some gold.
Because that means there's a chance I get more pearls.
There's one guy there that we can use.
You know what?
Actually, no.
I'm going to go to the fortress and do this.
Because they're also running around there.
And I need to kill the blaze guys.
Oh.
And a man.
Come at me.
This is the built-in defense perimeter.
Nice.
We even got a pearl.
That is wonderful.
Exquisite me.
Coming through.
Hot soup.
Okay.
We should make a proper...
dissension method here.
There we go.
Finally.
Ah, wait.
I should have brought my...
No, wait.
I don't have any fire protection potions.
I threw them away, didn't I?
Dang it.
How come these guys are not reacting?
Hello?
There's an intruder in your fortress.
You're just going to take that?
This guy saw me, though.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oof.
Scary feeling when you miss a shot.
There we go.
We got one.
Oh, no.
Be careful.
Oh, here they come.
Ow.
Oh, shit.
Ah, it's not a good idea to come here without fire protection, I don't think.
But now I'm here, right?
One down.
They even dropped a little rod for me.
Is that a skeleton?
How come he didn't shoot me when I was there?
Hello?
You can't get up here?
That's too bad.
He tried to crit me.
Shit.
Oh, my God.
That was scary.
I have no idea where they came from.
They must have dropped from the skies or something.
Man.
Where the blaze is at?
Hey, bro.
Usually I'm being bombarded with, like, lasers right now, but not this time.
Now I just have lasers in my shoes.
I actually never had lasers in my shoes.
Is that weird?
Oh, God.
Show me the goods.
How many do I have?
I have three.
That means I have six blaze thingies.
Blaze powders.
Or...
I forgot what it's called.
You know what I mean.
Come on.
Spawn.
I'm ready for you.
I'm here.
I'm waiting.
Where are you?
Oh.
I think I saw him.
Wait.
Did he actually drop one and then it fell down into the lava?
Jackie, come here.
I think it may have fallen down.
Nerve wracking.
There's no activity in this fortress today, huh?
This is embarrassing.
The defense you got going on here.
No problem.
That's ten.
I need to kill two more.
Or get two more rods.
Here we go.
I think if I walk away, there's like a higher chance.
It keeps happening when I walk away.
It's like when you cross a threshold.
Something.
Nope.
I'm imagining things.
Come on.
I'm not sure how it works.
Shit.
He hit me.
Oh.
Okay.
You don't want to fight on stairs.
Lesson learned.
They can hit you no matter what.
When you're in range.
I guess they hit my feet.
Oh.
You're over there now.
Never mind.
I'm already burning.
You can't do anything more to me.
Oh shit.
What the hell?
Oh.
Oh god.
I'm in danger.
Oh my god.
Well, that was scary.
I just need one more rod.
Come on.
Actually, I'm going to go kill this guy.
Did he drop one?
He did.
Nice.
That's mine.
Oh god.
Even got another one.
Shit.
He was dark soulsing me.
Hiding behind the corner, you know.
Raining to strike.
Eight rods.
Do we take one more?
Just, you know, for the road.
Something, uh...
We can nibble on as we go along.
I'm in the zone right now.
I can keep going.
Man, the bow is really effective.
There we go.
We got an extra.
Now I'm out.
Don't be too greedy now.
We're leaving.
On the way back, I'm gonna feed some pigs some gold.
Hopefully get another pearl or two.
That would be the icing on the cake.
Okay.
Who wants to eat some gold?
Oh.
Imagine if that was a big hole.
I almost stepped into it.
You.
I see you.
I see your tunic.
Look what I got for you.
I also have some for this guy over here.
Calm down.
I got it.
You know what?
Stay down there.
Don't go anywhere.
Feed me.
You stay there.
Wait, where did the other guy go?
Oh, he's over here.
Jackie, no.
Careful.
Did he fall down?
Where did he go?
You're trapped now.
You're mine.
You will forever work for me.
I saw this in the speedrun video.
They put them in like a little hole.
In fact, somehow they get like a lot.
I don't know how they do that.
But you can apparently like get a million of them.
It's coming, by the way.
I'm going to speedrun this game.
And you'll see some...
You'll see some real shit.
Come on.
Pearl me.
What is this crap you're giving me?
What even is that?
Okay, you're not going to come out until you give me a pearl.
You're going to stay down there and think about what you've done.
Or haven't done yet.
There's nobody else.
Actually, there's a guy over there.
But I don't know...
How many there are left here.
Visually, it looks like four, but there's probably more.
Another brick.
Come on.
Oh.
Okay.
That's one stack gone.
I like that he has to inspect the gold for it.
He's like, hmm, let me see.
Is this real gold or not?
All right, I guess it is.
And then he does the exact same thing for every one of them.
At this point, he should trust me.
I only give the good gold.
29 carats.
Oh, one left.
Come on, let it be the pearl.
Pearl me.
Ah, for crying out loud.
Okay, you're free to go.
But don't let me catch you out here again.
Without a pearl in hand.
Let's go back.
Basso!
That's Basso.
No, it's...
Yeah, it's Basso.
I can tell by the way he is.
What was I doing?
I talked myself out of it right now.
Oh, I even got fire resistance potions.
Oh, yeah, right.
Blaze.
All of it.
It's time.
Eyes of Ender.
Fourteen of them.
Oh, great Eye of Ender.
Show me the path.
Now.
Where the hell did you go?
We're going to try that again.
Yeah.
Eye of Ender.
Show me the path.
Go.
Where the...
Oh.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
I need to fix my inventory first.
Before we go on this trip.
Let's prepare.
It was a dark and stormy night.
No, I keep those.
String in there.
He's going in there.
Actually, another break.
I feel like...
I don't know what I feel like about this.
Exotic.
I guess.
We don't need gold where we're going.
Do need a shield though.
A better one.
A new shield.
A fresh shield.
Sheer.
We're gonna burn the last one.
Cat.
Nice.
Maybe need more arrows for this.
This is an arrow boss.
Okay.
Armor is here.
We don't need this right now.
Take already.
Maybe some ascension blocks and...
We're ready to go.
Oh, let's bring a bed as well.
Yeah.
That's it.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Oh, and a boat.
Can't forget the boat.
I will find this so fast.
I think maybe there's something about the angle that it's...
Like, the higher it goes, the further maybe.
Something like that.
And the way I saw that one go up...
I'm guesstimating about...
14.
There's no units.
It's just...
It's 14.
That's the answer.
Don't believe me?
Watch.
We're at 11 now.
13.
Okay.
Let's get up there so we can see now.
We're at 14 exactly.
Oh, great eye of Ender!
Show me thy path!
And that's approximately...
That's about 9.
You saw it, right?
Okay.
A little further.
Wait.
I can't get lost.
Ah, but I know where I am.
I went northwest.
Hey, more dogs!
But I don't have bones.
Too bad.
No great eye of Ender.
Where are they?
In my mouth!
Ah!
I got it.
Okay, this is it.
If it's still pointing in the same direction, I'm gonna try something else to see exactly how far away it is.
Let's see what it says.
Okay, motherfucker.
Okay.
So watch.
So it's like...
There.
Right there.
What am I...
Oh no.
I wasn't looking!
That's gone.
No, it's here.
Oh, it floats.
Nice.
The other one was over here.
It should float.
There it is.
Nice.
Dude, I love that they float.
Nothing like wet meat in the evening.
Ew.
That's disturbing.
Actually, you know what?
Maybe it's easier on a boat.
Hold on.
This is gonna be way easier.
Check it out.
We're gonna do one here.
That way.
Let's see how much that varies now.
The bigger the variation, the closer.
I will show you exactly where it is.
I'm so confident, I don't need these pearls.
I'm gonna end up right on the spot.
You'll see what I mean.
I'll show you.
It is exactly...
You see how the...
Yeah, the gravitational field is congregating.
We're close.
It is right...
Here!
Over there, I mean.
Hold on.
A little further.
It's right here.
Yep.
I told you it was around this spot.
So where exactly?
Is it like right here?
It's like right here.
I wanna be exact here.
A little this way.
Okay.
Oh no.
Come here.
Was it right below me?
How's it right below?
All right, we're doing the diver thing.
Falling backwards.
Guys, I'm gonna dig down.
I have no fear.
Think I'm afraid?
Wait, wait, hold on.
This may be a bad idea.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's not dig straight down.
It's a bad idea.
I feel like I've learned my lesson.
You'll see.
It's okay.
Calm down now.
I know.
It's gonna be alright.
First things first.
The bit.
Oh, it's...
Thunderstorm?
Oh, really?
Interesting.
So we only have 10 eyes, by the way.
I don't remember if we need...
10.
Or 12.
It's either 10, 12, or 16.
But something tells me it's gotta be 12.
What's up, brother man?
I have come to invade your castle.
Hi!
Dude!
Books!
Oh my god, it's beautiful!
It's what I need!
Yes!
That's amazing.
That's even unintended side effect.
That's unbreakable, apparently.
Wow.
Literally cannot be broken.
Oh, this is exciting.
Emergency lights.
I'm stealing this entire library.
It's mine now.
Oh, my pickaxe is about to break.
That's bad.
Oh, look at this!
Secret found!
That's a terrible secret.
What's this way?
I see you there.
In fact, I have wallhack now.
Guys!
I don't need to...
Uh...
Maze this!
I can smell it!
It's this way!
No, it's...
It's the...
My nose is never wrong.
It's this way.
Hold on.
Ah, got you, didn't I?
Acting.
You thought I...
Knew how to trust my nose.
I didn't.
Oh!
Ew!
All right, fine.
I guess I'll take that.
I feel like the rewards in these chests are...
Kind of underwhelming.
Oh, shit.
I'm back where I started.
Let's go deeper.
Dude, I...
Every time I go downstairs, I want to press control...
To slide, you know?
Hey, hello!
Mr. President?
Nice prison you got here.
Nerd.
Wait.
Why is this damn portal always so hard to find?
I swear to God, there's never...
A situation where you just find it.
You know?
It's always trials and tribulations and bullshit.
You gotta go through the worst imaginable...
Case of being lost.
To find this shit.
Four hits.
Because of the armor, I guess.
Do I trust?
I trust...
I trust instinct.
God, I'm good.
Okay, now.
Oh, no.
We don't have enough!
Why did I leave one pearl behind in the ocean?
Man.
That's rough.
Shit.
That's okay.
I'm sure I can find another pearl in here somewhere.
Bread, huh?
What are you doing in there?
Are you a prison...
A prisoner in the prison?
I don't know why I had so much trouble saying that.
Let's end the site.
Well!
Okay, here's the plan.
I'm going to go back...
To the portal area.
Wait, I don't know where it was.
This way.
And then I'm going to dig up.
Straight up.
And at the very top...
There's going to be...
An enderman.
And this enderman has a pearl with my name on it.
And also, it's going to be night.
Which will put me at a two for two.
And if I am right about that...
It means I can probably get a medium-sized candy bag tonight.
Not just a small one.
We should hit water anytime.
Oh wait, that's the problem.
Then I can't find it later.
Oh no.
Here we go.
So here it is.
We're going to make a little thingy here.
This is my statue of greatness.
This is what it looks like.
Oh my god!
Wait a second.
Wait a minute.
I wonder.
Does the eye point directly to the portal?
If I had been more spot on here.
Interesting.
Look!
Exactly where this is gravitated.
On my...
Statue of greatness.
S.O.G.
So what I'm going to do...
Is this.
I will park my boat right here.
This is where it is.
Yep.
I'm going to go over there now.
No I'm not.
Because I need...
Oh no!
Fuck.
We need...
Blaze powder!
Gah!
But you know what?
I do want to go home with these books anyway.
So it's all good.
It's all good.
Man.
Wait.
Which way is home?
Fuck.
I didn't bring a compass.
But wait a minute.
I...
Ah!
Urine!
I can't believe it.
How do I get back?
I...
I think it was this...
No wait.
I went northwest.
I know how to get back.
Southeast.
Speed!
It's speed!
Yeah!
Faster!
Thank you so much!
Yes!
Oh wait.
I don't...
I...
Right.
My...
My fucking bed is in the...
Oh my god.
Oh!
We can't...
Oh no.
I need a bed.
I don't...
Shit!
Dude!
There's no sun!
Jackie!
Not now!
So wait.
Hold on.
I mean...
It's that way.
The moon rises in the east as well.
I have decided so.
Oh my god.
No.
It's gonna be a shitty way home.
Uh...
Okay.
I'm swimming!
No wait.
I can make a boat.
We don't need wool for that.
Wait.
I have...
Uh...
Oh no.
Make one of these.
Boat.
Gimme.
Okay.
Go.
Holy crap!
We're going southeast.
Towards home.
And I will not forget where it is.
Because we have a boat there now.
And it's wonderful.
And I love this music!
What the hell is this even?
This is some nice music playing.
Oh!
Lava?
Not what I'm looking for.
I remember this spot.
Fourth period.
1980.
Good times.
What's going on over there?
Little skeleton party.
Good thing I'm not invited.
I just thought of a funny ass joke, dude.
I'm in danger.
I just feel the pull of home right now.
You feel it?
It's right over here.
Ish.
I think I'm right.
Come on.
We go home.
We grab the pearls.
We grab the blaze.
And we go back.
And we finally enter the portal.
Get away from me!
Cool guys don't look at explosions.
Go, go, go!
It's right over here.
What the hell?
We got a ding guy down there.
Except he's not really a ding guy, is he?
We need to earn that rule.
And he hasn't earned it.
God, I hope I'm going the right way.
I'm actually not entirely sure.
Where the fuck am I?
Wait, what if I...
Oh no.
I don't recognize this.
What if I was wrong about the moon?
No, no, no.
I know where I am.
Wait!
I need you, I need you.
Come here, bastard.
Come here.
Come to me!
Come here!
Ow!
Fucking skeletons!
The worst time for them!
No!
Shit!
Why did the skeletons have to come out?
We got a pearl.
See you, nerd.
Holy shit, that was close.
My heart could not have...
Oh man, imagine.
I would have spawned in the dam.
Oh no, that would have been terrible.
I know where I am though.
We're home.
Man, this game really makes you afraid of dying.
He thought it could encroach on my land.
Sorry, I had to get my aggressions out.
I just had something building up inside of me, you know?
Oh, look at these cookies.
This is what you want to come home to.
Am I right?
Tell me I have more.
Yes!
I have exactly two!
When I need one.
Nice!
That's exactly what I almost need.
Now...
This is the wrong spot for it.
Dip, dip, dip.
Dirt.
Seagrass!
Hmm.
Can I do anything with that?
I got doors.
That's nice.
Nice.
Let's bring them.
Let's not forget to bring them.
Uh...
Wait.
Did I use all my blaze stuff?
Nice!
I had one extra.
Just to be safe.
You know.
In case I get lost.
I'm not gonna get lost, but just in case.
Now, the only mission I have now, is I need to arrive at the location with one.
So I can go crazy with the other two.
But I need one.
That's it.
Uno.
And guess who's dying?
Not me.
The winged beast of the underworld shall fall to my arrows.
Or maybe we employ the bed technique.
I saw that also in the speedrun.
Where they put a bed up somewhere, and then they just fucking explode it.
It looks so stupid.
But we can try it, I guess.
But I don't have any beds, so maybe some other time.
Or maybe I bring...
I don't have any TNT either.
Never mind.
It would be fun to try, though.
But you would need something that doesn't...
Yeah, wait.
How do you not get hit by the explosion, though?
I guess you make a blast shield or something?
Like an LOS thing?
Must be.
By the way, I'm totally going off fields here.
I'm vibe-navigating.
Vibe-gating.
I think it's a...
About this way.
What's up, cow?
Not even gonna collect your meat, because I'm evil like that.
I'd do it for sport.
I just hate cows.
I hate them all.
I hate them.
I hate cows.
I do like those tall trees.
I think a base up there would be kind of nuts.
Like there's snow, but it's not like crazy snow, you know?
Because over here, you have non-snow area.
So that would give me the opportunity to be close to something that is like snow without being in the snow.
Right?
That sounds nice.
Haven't used the pearl yet?
I know where it is.
I know.
I'm grabbing this.
Eh, wait.
Buried treasure map here?
In this economy?
What the hell?
We're gonna look for that afterwards.
We kill the dragon, and then we go look for a treasure.
Oh, it should be around...
Did I pass it already?
It's like over here, isn't it?
No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
I think I went...
It's a little further.
It's not yet.
Right?
It's not...
Let me just double check.
It is not here!
It's the next.
Okay.
I don't remember this island, though.
That's what's...
You know, messing me up right now.
Look for gravitational anomalies.
What the hell?
Oh, wait, is that...
Oh, that's a boat.
Right.
It's a boat.
Wait, I don't...
Maybe I recognize this?
It's like over here somewhere.
God, we may need to...
We may have to use a pearl.
I don't want to say the P word, but...
No!
There it is!
Fuck, I'm good.
Oh, my God.
I'm actually kind of impressed with myself.
That's nice.
Look at the anomalous nature components.
Bouncing and medicine and...
Ah, but hold on.
We have to do this.
And I'm safe to dig down, because I know what I did.
I made this hole.
I know what's in it.
There's no danger.
There we are.
And...
Wait, what?
Oh.
Next time!
Next time we kill the dragon.
Yeah.
I was gonna do it right before the portal, but I couldn't resist jumping in!
I just had to do it.
Next time we're gonna have a ball, though.
Ah, that was nice.
That was some good old-fashioned damn Minecraft, wasn't it?
That felt really good.
That was good for the soul right there.
Very nice.
Oliver, did you say tripod on purpose?
No, I keep forgetting what it's actually called.
It's one of those words that I just...
Cannot remember for the life of me.
What is it?
So I just default to tripod, you know?
Because I don't remember the word.
Oh, trident.
Right!
I don't know why I cannot remember that word!
It's insane.
Yeah, the cogs move with the chat.
You guys are making the cogs spin.
Spinning cogs.
Impressive orienteering, my good sir.
Thank you, thank you.
I appreciate that, Ajatelenko.
Man, I nailed your name.
Are you aware that Billy Basso is the name of the animal well-deaf?
Yes!
That's why I named him Billy Basso.
His middle name is actually Bruno.
You didn't know that, did you?
Boom!
Gotcha.
Did you hear about vanilla tweaks?
I know you mentioned that you didn't want to add any other mods, but I feel like this one you would love.
It's not a mod, really.
It changes smaller features based on what you pick.
Like, for example, making your shield take less space on your screen.
Oh.
I don't think so.
I'm just gonna stick with what I know right now.
But thank you for the suggestion, though.
Maybe it's something I'll look into.
We'll see.
It's like an extra or, like, expanded options menu or something, I imagine, right?
I think it's very cool that you don't use cords to navigate.
I don't understand why anyone does it, though.
It does...
It feel...
Okay.
Here's my really weird and apparently unpopular opinion on this.
And I feel like it shouldn't even be controversial at all to say.
I feel like the, uh...
The coordinates thing was something that was left in the game by accident when it released.
I'm pulling this out of my ass, by the way.
And everyone just went with it.
And then they left it in forever.
It doesn't feel like something that belongs in the game.
Am I crazy?
Yeah, it's a debugging tool.
Like, how are people looking at that as, like, part of the core gameplay?
That, to me, is bonkers.
It's insanity.
If I used that, I would feel like I'm cheating.
And I wouldn't be satisfied.
You know?
True.
Man, that game is loud right now.
Calm it down a bit.
Because it's nature of the game with infinite grit.
Yeah, but it's called a debug menu.
You're not...
The player is not supposed to see this.
It's a development tool.
Right?
It also doesn't feel like it's part of the game.
Like, it looks wrong and weird.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm weird with that.
Some people seem to agree with me, though.
So I can't be the only one.
What are you having for dinner?
I am having leftovers, actually.
I made some cotyleda ifel the other day when I had some people over.
And there's leftovers.
It is basically pork chops that you quickly fry on the pan just to get them a little brown.
But not finished frying.
You put them in a large oven pan.
Baking pan, I guess.
And then you make some tomato, mushroom, you know, red, yellow, green pepper cream sauce.
With onions and stuff like that, you know.
And you pour that over the pork chops.
And then you put it in the oven and it becomes nice and crispy on top.
And it's amazing.
And then you eat it with the rice.
It's so good.
I promise you.
You would love it.
When is next stream?
Very soon.
Probably in a couple days.
Tonight or tomorrow, I'm gonna keep playing Detroit Become Human.
Because I haven't even played it since the first episode.
And I kind of want to get back into it.
So I'm gonna do that probably a lot tomorrow.
And then the day after tomorrow, I think I'm gonna stream again.
Yeah.
That sounds like the plan.
No episode today.
Unless I somehow managed to upload it late.
But I don't know.
We'll see.
Will humans become Detroit someday?
Maybe.
Maybe that is in your future, Urarumi.
You will become a city.
I heard that Detroit is, or was, I don't know if it still is, but, like, the main car manufacturing city in America?
Right?
They had, like, some big factories there making cars and stuff?
Not anymore?
Oh, okay.
Motor City.
Right.
I see.
Heavy on was.
Oh, alright.
So what is the city like now?
All I know about Detroit is that they used to make cars, and that M&M was from there, you know?
It's not great?
It's the birthplace of techno.
Oh!
Because of put your hands up for Detroit?
I love this city.
Do-do-do-do-do-do.
That's what I think of every time I hear Detroit.
You were late today for six minutes.
You have to stay for six minutes more.
Yeah, but think about it.
I also made the countdown smaller.
Usually I put that around twice what I had, right?
I think it evens out.
Also, Jackie is really aggressively rubbing herself against my leg, because she wants to eat now, and it's time.
It's actually a little overtime on that.
Genuine question, Oliver.
Do you believe that become human is realistic?
Like, I feel...
Are you...
Hold on, I'm not gonna read anymore.
I feel like you're about to maybe spoil something.
I don't know if you are, but I'm not gonna read it.
But if you're asking whether or not I think it's a real representation of the future, I would say there's a high chance of it, yeah.
Just especially with everything that's been happening lately, the amount of progress we're making with technology is absolutely insane.
If it's gonna be exactly like the game, I'd probably not, right?
But I think there's some truth to that somewhere.
Eat Oliver...
No, she's not gonna eat me.
She would never do that to me.
Does your music mod include the latest updates?
It should, yeah.
I think I did collect most of it.
From the new versions.
But I can double check.
26.2.
I don't know when that one came out, but I can check that.
What's the story of the potatoes?
There's not really a big story behind it.
It's just that I once mentioned that I really like to make baked potatoes in the microwave because it's super convenient and fast.
And that became kind of a meme because people thought it was weird.
Like, I get it, the best ones are made in the oven and it takes a while, right?
But the microwave ones are pretty damn good, man.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah, the recipe is in the Discord.
When did 26.2 come out, though?
Are we talking, like, a couple weeks ago or months?
You can just suggest it here, Senator, or just put it in a channel on Discord, the one called Channel Related.
The thing is, though, it's already so long, the backlog, that it's like almost a little drop in a big pond now, right?
But feel free to recommend the game.
I'll put it on the backlog if you say it's good.
Do you miss bundles?
Honestly, with the toolboxes, not so much.
They kind of fill out the same hole.
For me.
I just need to make more toolboxes, basically.
Will you ever purge the backlog?
No way.
Why would I do that?
The only way that backlog is getting purged is by playing it.
I will stream KSP.
At some point, for sure, man.
I've had the itch to play that ever since...
The Artemis stuff with NASA, you know?
Because I got the itch against, like, oh yeah, that's awesome.
I want to get into that, yeah.
Yeah, I should have prepared for the dragon.
You know what?
You know what it was?
So I was going along the path to...
What is the place called?
The one underwater?
Where the portal is in.
What is that place called?
There's a name for it.
I forget it.
It's not fortress.
Stronghold.
That's the one.
So, on my way to the stronghold, I was so focused on following these pearls that I completely forgot that I also needed pearls for the portal.
So I was like, oh, I have plenty of pearls to find this place, you know?
And then, right before I found the portal, I was like, oh yeah, wait.
I need these for the thing, you know?
So that...
If I had thought about that, I wouldn't have left those two pearls that I left in the water.
Because I left those two thinking, oh, I have plenty to get there.
That's the only thing I thought about.
It's not like I just threw them to be funny, you know?
I really thought I had more than I needed.
And I was too lazy to go get them.
That's what it was.
It was a hubris thing, yep.
Oh, it's three pearls I left?
Oh no.
Oh wait.
Two pearls for sure there, and then...
Yeah, one of them I couldn't find after throwing it.
I was like, where did it go?
It just disappeared.
Oh yeah.
Uh, I'm genuinely curious.
Are there some aspects of the base game that you feel like...
They were explored more?
I feel like personally there is tons of missed potential.
And the oceans are like having volcano biomes or something.
I mean, you can dream up a number of things that you would want added to the game, right?
But I don't know.
I'm not a game developer.
I wouldn't know, honestly.
It's a tough question.
Because if you start to add a lot of stuff to it, you know, then it's at some point it's not Minecraft anymore.
I don't know.
It's a really tough one.
Okay.
I'm gonna go.
It's feeding time.
Thank you so much for watching.
Tomorrow it's gonna be Detroit.
And stream again the day after tomorrow.
So yeah.
Have a good one.
Thank you for showing up.
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.